Nyanko Days!
Oh, it's getting dark.
I should hurry home, or Elsa will be angry.
Bye-bye, Yuuko-chan.
Say hi to your kitties for me.
Okay.
See you tomorrow!
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
I know it'd make Elsa angry,
but I wish we could have hung out longer.
Achoo!
Someone is talking about cute little me.
Elsa
(Turkish Angora)
I suppose Azumi will be home late.
Hmph! It's not as if I'm lonely by myself!
It's not as if I'm lonely...
Evening
Azumi, you were home late today.
Did something good happen?
Yeah, I made a really cute new friend.
Even cuter than me?
Yeah!
Squee!
No hesitation at all...
I've never seen you look so happy talking about someone else before.
You might be right.
I wanted to be Yuuko-chan's friend from the moment I saw her.
I had trouble talking to her at first since she didn't seem to be the social type,
but I'm so happy we finally became friends.
Hmm...
Why did you want to be her friend so badly?
Because I thought her kitty hair ties were really cute!
That's why?
Every day nyan nyan nyan nya
Every day we meow meow meow mew
Every night gorogoro
Every night we purr purr
Every time mogumogu shitai n da na
Every time we just wanna eat
Anytime wagamama ja nai nya my pace
We're not selfish, we'll go at your pace anytime
Koakuma nyanko
We're such naughty kitties
I love you
Je t'aime
Suki desu
I love you
Nyanko is LOVE!
Would they look good on me too?
Azumi and Elsa