Nyanko Days.
Ran, you're really fired up.
Of course. I never slack off,
no matter what I compete in.
That's our Ran!
Smug!
God, you're so cool!
The Marathon
Begins
Wow, Iketani-san is fast.
But Azumi-chan's not far behind!
Uuugh...
And my side already hurts...
This is so easy, I feel a yawn coming on.
Stop
A Few
Minutes Later
Huh?
Why is Iketani-san still standing here?
And her legs are shaking like crazy!
What is she so scared of?
Huh?!
Meow!
I see. So you don't like cats, Iketani-san?
That's right.
I'm scared of cats. How lame is that?
No one's ever found out until now...
Everyone's gonna make fun of me.
But everyone has something they can't deal with.
Your friends won't make fun of you
just because they know what yours is.
There are tons of things I can't handle well.
What's your name?
Uh... Konagai Yuuko.
Konagai-san...
Thanks.
Blush
Wh-Why are you the one blushing?!
Every day nyan nyan nyan nya
Every day we meow meow meow mew
Every night gorogoro
Every night we purr purr
Every time mogumogu shitai n da na
Every time we just wanna eat
Anytime wagamama ja nai nya my pace
We're not selfish, we'll go at your pace anytime
Koakuma nyanko
We're such naughty kitties
I love you
Je t'aime
Suki desu
I love you
Nyanko is LOVE!
I'll remember this!
I thought she was scary,
but she's actually pretty cute.
Wait! I forgot about the marathon!
Secrets and Tsundere
She tried her
hardest and
managed to
finish.