Nyanko Days!
Sunday
All right. I'm finally gonna beat this game today.
Yuuko! Your fingers look fun!
Hey, wait!
I wanna play, too!
Yuuko, want a snack?
Sure!
I'll get out the chips I
bought recently, too.
Stare
Wow! So this is what they call "thrilling"!
Honestly, I can't bear to watch you sometimes.
Sowwy.
Sad
That sound I heard... I should've known.
Thanks for always helping me out, Rou.
Good kitty.
It's not like being praised makes me happy or anything...
Purr
You're purring like crazy.
I've had it!
Waaaa
I can't draw it right!
That's not true, Shii.
It's a lovely fish.
That's you, Yuuko-san.
Huh?!
Here, Shii. Open up.
Cat Biscuit
It's a good thing Shii loves biscuits so much.
Stare...
Every day nyan nyan nyan nya
Every day we meow meow meow mew
Every night gorogoro
Every night we purr purr
Every time mogumogu shitai n da na
Every time we just wanna eat
Anytime wagamama ja nai nya my pace
We're not selfish, we'll go at your pace anytime
Koakuma nyanko
We're such naughty kitties
I love you
Je t'aime
Suki desu
I love you
Nyanko is LOVE!
Nom, nom, nom, nom...
Weekend with Cats 1