Nyanko Days!
TV would be easy because all we have to do is look at it.
Why don't we do that?
The government's response to this issue...
TV! I wanna watch!
Good idea!
Stare
Serious.
Future discussions will be...
This is boring!
...a topic that—
Time for kitty calisthenics!
Change it back!
This kind of thing is boring for me!
No!
Wh-What do I do?
I have to make them be friends again...
H-Here. Why not play with this together?
Hmph!
What can I do?
I'm home.
Yuuko-san!
Shii, what's wrong?
I wanted us all to have fun playing together,
Sniffle
and we thought it'd be really fun to imitate you.
But the other two had a fight, and now I'm sad!
Come here, you two.
Cat Tunnel
— New Toy!
Ta-da!
Know what this is?
Hey Rou, isn't this fun?
It is.
Um... I'm sorry about before.
No, I'm the one who's sorry.
Every day nyan nyan nyan nya
Every day we meow meow meow mew
Every night gorogoro
Every night we purr purr
Every time mogumogu shitai n da na
Every time we just wanna eat
Anytime wagamama ja nai nya my pace
We're not selfish, we'll go at your pace anytime
Koakuma nyanko
We're such naughty kitties
I love you
Je t'aime
Suki desu
I love you
Nyanko is LOVE!
I'm so glad they're friends again.
Uh-huh.
Messy...
The Cats' Day Part 2
I have to clean all this up...
Messy...