Nyanko Days!
Hmm, a local festival...
I don't like crowds, though. What should I do?
What's a festival? I wanna go!
Sparkle
C'mon, let's go!
Oh, all right. Let's get Shii and Rou and we'll all go together.
Wow!
How gorgeous!
What's that all about?
Dazzling
It's Yuuko-chan!
Azumi-chan?!
Dazzling
I just got here, too.
Let's walk around together.
S-Sure.
Will you little ones walk around with us, too?
Y...
Awed
Yes!
Strangers are scary... Strangers are scary...
Shy Around
Strangers
Look at all the fishies!
Can we eat them?
No, that would definitely be a bad idea.
You react just like a little kitten.
I'm not a kitten!
Oh? Then let's see you prove it!
We caught lots of them.
Let's go over there next.
Okay.
All right, let's do this.
Whoever catches the most fish wins.
Fine! I'm gonna win!
Right, Yuuko?
Huh?
Azumi?
Every day nyan nyan nyan nya
Every day we meow meow meow mew
Every night gorogoro
Every night we purr purr
Every time mogumogu shitai n da na
Every time we just wanna eat
Anytime wagamama ja nai nya my pace
We're not selfish, we'll go at your pace anytime
Koakuma nyanko
We're such naughty kitties
I love you
Je t'aime
Suki desu
I love you
Nyanko is LOVE!
What do I do? Maa's gone!
So is Elsa. When did they get separated from us?
Let's head back the way we came for now.
Okay.
So...
The Worst Senses of Direction.
Which way did we come from again?
Lets Go to the Festival
These two are hopeless.