Nyanko Days!
I, Konagai Yuuko, have never done very well at school.
A few months after starting high school
I still can't talk to the other kids,
and now just look at me.
I have no friends.
Oh, wow!
Shiratori Azumi-san...
Stare...
Well, I guess popular people like her live in a totally different world from me.
Another exhausting day...
I'm home.
Welcome home!
I'm home, my kitties!
Mushy
There's really no place like home.
I have three cats.
Gn
aw
A mischievous munchkin named Maa...
Gn
aw
Yuuko, did you make any friends?
Ta-da !
A laid-back Singapura named Shii...
Maa-san, friends aren't made overnight.
Right, Rou-san?
Lepidopterology
Hmm . . .
And a level-headed Russian blue named Rou.
Lepidopterology
Actually, maybe I should go to school with you...
You're all such angels! Cats rock!
Cuddle
Every day nyan nyan nyan nya
Every day we meow meow meow mew
Every night gorogoro
Every night we purr purr
Every time mogumogu shitai n da na
Every time we just wanna eat
Anytime wagamama ja nai nya maipeesu
We're not selfish, we'll go at your pace anytime
Koakuma nyanko
We're such naughty kitties
I love you
Je t'aime
Suki desu
I love you
Nyanko is LOVE!
Pet
Yuuko, how long are you going to stay in the entryway?
Me and My Kitties
Pet