Nyanko Days!
I'm done with my homework.
Why don't we go for a walk?
Sunday
Afternoon
Yeah!
Is there anywhere you want to go?
Um...
That high place we went to before!
Okay then, I'll race you there!
Yay!
The view from here sure is beautiful, isn't it?
Oh, you're...
Huh?!
Konagai-san from my class, right?
Sh-Sh-Shiratori-san?
Why... are you here?
This is my family's property.
Aside from being popular, she's legit bourgeois!
But anyway...
So you also have cats, Konagai-san?
And three of them! Wow!
I always wanted a friend I could talk to about cats.
Let's be friends, okay?
O-Okay...
Whoops, look at the time.
It's almost time for my lesson.
Let's talk again on Monday, okay?
Bye-bye!
B-Bye-bye.
That was nerve-wracking!
Every day nyan nyan nyan nya
Every day we meow meow meow mew
Every night gorogoro
Every night we purr purr
Every time mogumogu shitai n da na
Every time we just wanna eat
Anytime wagamama ja nai nya my pace
We're not selfish, we'll go at your pace anytime
Koakuma nyanko
We're such naughty kitties
I love you
Je t'aime
Suki desu
I love you
Nyanko is LOVE!
Today sure was surprising.
I never expected to make a friend that way.
It's all thanks to you three.
Weekend with Cats 2
Thanks for always being there.