Nyanko Days!
Sulk
It's boring without Yuuko.
Oh, come on. We can't help that she's at school.
Do you think Yuuko-san was able to talk to that girl okay?
Nope, not at all!
There were so many people around
I couldn't even get close, let alone talk to her.
Konagai-san...
Shiratori-san, the principal wanted to see you about your award.
I'll never be able to talk to her this way.
Ugh, I just wanna go home and cuddle my cats...
Nya hee hee
Rub Rub
Maa loves having her tummy rubbed...
Nya hee hee
Rub Rub
Purr
Rou likes rubs under her chin...
And Shii likes rubs under her arms.
Stretch
You little weirdo...
I'm such a coward.
I'll just go home.
Konagai-san!
Sh-Shiratori-san?
I'm so glad you haven't left yet!
Let's walk home together.
O-Okay...
We can stop at a coffee shop too, if you want.
What is this turning into?
Every day nyan nyan nyan nya
Every day we meow meow meow mew
Every night gorogoro
Every night we purr purr
Every time mogumogu shitai n da na
Every time we just wanna eat
Anytime wagamama ja nai nya my pace
We're not selfish, we'll go at your pace anytime
Koakuma nyanko
We're such naughty kitties
I love you
Je t'aime
Suki desu
I love you
Nyanko is LOVE!
Since your family's rich,
I thought you'd come to and from school by car.
Well, I used to, but...
I found someone I want to walk home with,
Last
Night
so from tomorrow on, I won't need you to drive me.
Shock
So that's why.
Yuuko and Azumi
Wh-When you put it that way, it sounds kinda...