Nyanko Days!
Where could Maa and Elsa-chan have gone?
Shiratori Azumi!
I've found you at last!
I challenge you to an eating contest!
Iketani-san!
Did you see any cats over there?
N-N-No, I haven't seen any cats! Stop that!
Okay. Thanks.
Where did Yuuko go?
Hey! Wait a minute!
Well, you walk too slow, Elsa.
I always ride in Azumi's bag or on her shoulder,
so I had no idea walking for long periods was this tiring...
If you're too slow, I'll leave you behind.
B-But I asked you to wait!
I was just kidding. Come on, let's hurry.
We'll never find them at this rate.
I'll never see Azumi again...
It'll be okay.
I'm gonna find both Azumi and Yuuko.
So cheer up, Elsa!
Elsa, I've got a great idea!
Yuuko! Azumi!
Azumi-chan, look!
How did those two get up there?
Yuuko! Yuuko! Yu-u-ko!
Oh! I see Yuuko! Hey, Yuuko!
Gah!
I have to stop her, quick!
At any rate, I'm glad we found both of them.
On The
Way Home
Case closed, huh?
Hey, Yuuko, I had a lot of fun today!
Every day nyan nyan nyan nya
Every day we meow meow meow mew
Every night gorogoro
Every night we purr purr
Next time, I wanna sing on the stage with Elsa!
Every time mogumogu shitai n da na
Every time we just wanna eat
Hey! Don't make that decision on your own!
Anytime wagamama ja nai nya my pace
We're not selfish, we'll go at your pace anytime
W-Well, I wouldn't mind coming
here with you again, though...
Koakuma nyanko
We're such naughty kitties
Really? Then let's do kitty calisthenics on the stage!
I love you
I'm not doing that!
Je t'aime
I love you
Anyway, you two...
Suki desu
I love you
You're such good friends all of a sudden.
Nyanko is LOVE!
Did something happen?
That's a secret!
With Our Cats
Yep!
Nyanko is LOVE!
See You Again♪