Nyanko Days!
This is it.
Since she said she'd take me to a coffee shop,
I wondered what kind of fancy place it'd be.
I'm glad it actually seems... normal?!
Sh-Shiratori-san, th-this place
is s-s-super expensive...
Don't worry. My family runs this shop.
Shiratori
Um, I'll have an iced coffee.
It's the cheapest thing they have.
Okay then, I'll take two pancakes.
Huh? Two?
You ordered the cheapest thing to be considerate, didn't you?
Pout
None of that, okay? Let's eat together.
Is she a goddess?
I've started calling you by your first name without realizing it, Yuuko-chan.
You can call me Azumi, too.
A-Azu...
Uh-huh.
Azu, Azu...
Azu, Azu, Azu, Azu...
Is that too hot? But it's iced coffee.
Not that...
Azumi... chan!
Yuuko-chan...
Azumi-chan!
Yuuko-chan.
Yuuko-chan!
Every day nyan nyan nyan nya
Every day we meow meow meow mew
Every night gorogoro
Every night we purr purr
Every time mogumogu shitai n da na
Every time we just wanna eat
Anytime wagamama ja nai nya my pace
We're not selfish, we'll go at your pace anytime
Koakuma nyanko
We're such naughty kitties
I love you
Je t'aime
Suki desu
I love you
Nyanko is LOVE!
Come to think of it,
we haven't talked about our cats yet.
You're a cat owner too, aren't you?
You had it with you the other day, right?
That's right.
You seem to practically sparkle when the subject of cats comes up, Yuuko-chan.
So if we talk about cats a lot,
will I get to see more of sparkly Yuuko-chan?
First Time Out Together
I'm so embarrassed...