I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Before I knew it, your colors were painted across the sky
I want you to hear what I have to say
For some reason, we won't understand each other
Until that time comes
Hopefully it'll sit right with you
Unsteady times like these will go by, however
Sorry for always causing you problems
Ah, I love you
I love you
I want you to know that
Closed today
You mean me?
Yes.
There's a lot we should know, right?
I was thinking it's about time you told us.
Okay, I'll talk!
Where did you come from, Miton?
A different world than this one.
What's that world like?
It's kind of...
like this.
I have no clue what that's supposed to be.
I see.
Then I'll project an image of what I remember it looking like.
You can do that?
Yep, I can.
Then do it.
Here I go!
It looks like this.
I don't get it.
Uh, what are those?
People, of course.
Those are people?!
When was it, I wonder...
Huh?
Miton!
Everyone!
Attention, everyone!
It's time for you to get the bracelet
that turns people into magical girls.
Okay!
And then our journey began.
It was an extremely harsh one.
We overcame so many hardships.
And made so many sacrifices.
And then I finally made it to the summit
of the mountain where the bracelet resided.
Everyone...
I'll do it.
I'll find the magical girl who fits this bracelet
and save the world!
So that's what happened.
All lies.
Gulp!
Miton made all of that up.
Our world is much more advanced and complex.
It's not that simple.
Mafuyu-san.
Gotcha!
Pochi-san, you and Miton are colleagues, right?
We were colleagues.
You were?
We were indeed,
but it's not as if we were close or anything.
We don't have anything to do
with each other anymore.
We didn't even try to find each other.
I just ran into Miton by chance.
Yuzuka, Chiya, you're my only friends right now.
Um...
We're sorry.
They're pitying me!
To be continued!
To Be Continued