I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Before I knew it, your colors were painted across the sky
I want you to hear what I have to say
For some reason, we won't understand each other
Until that time comes
Hopefully it'll sit right with you
Unsteady times like these will go by, however
Sorry for always causing you problems
Ah, I love you
I love you
I want you to know that
Transform!
Come on, Yuzuka-chan! Do yours, too!
R-Right.
T-Transform.
It's just as cute as I imagined!
A swimsuit...
Is she an exhibitionist?
I kind of have the same suspicion.
Wait a minute.
Huh?
One Minute Later
Wow. Beaks can open pretty wide, huh?
Let's see how far it'll go.
They get along so well.
Hey, show me your magic.
Uh, sure.
I can't wait.
Water, huh?
That's so cool!
What type of magic do you have, Mafuyu-san?
Well...
Chiya-chan, toss Pochi-kun this way.
Sure.
Watch this!
A bag, huh?
Yeah.
I can control its size, too.
That's a great ability.
Poor Pochi...
I wish I had your outfit, Mafuyu-san.
Having a swimsuit is weird.
Why a swimsuit?
A swimsuit?!
It's embarrassing walking outside,
or even just when I'm at home.
Why a swimsuit?
A swimsuit?!
That makes sense.
Why a swimsuit?
A swimsuit?!
But if you wear it all the time,
maybe you'll get used to it!
She's not on my side?!
But I like your outfit.
Huh?
It looks cute on you.
You should be more confident.
Come here and transform with
me until you get used to it.
B-But wouldn't you have to close shop?
Temporarily Closed
We close it all the time anyways.
Maybe your grandpa should
cut back on the games.
I've suggested that before, but...
Girl encountered!
That swimsuit looks like a rare item
I got after splashing my cash!
I guess you value attack power more than defense!
At least he's healthy.
Yeah, but kind of sick in the head, really.
Your outfit is really cute, but I can't wait to see Chiya-chan's too.
It's too bad we can't transform together, though.
Huh?
Well, once I retire, I think Pochi-kun
will go to Chiya-chan, so...
Chiya-chan...
Chiya-chan's going to...
be a magical girl?!
To be continued!
To Be Continued