I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Before I knew it, your colors were painted across the sky
I want you to hear what I have to say
For some reason, we won't understand each other
Until that time comes
Hopefully it'll sit right with you
Unsteady times like these will go by, however
Sorry for always causing you problems
Ah, I love you
I love you
I want you to know that
Hold on a second!
You're supposed to wear a swimsuit at the beach.
Let's go swimming.
Huh?
Daiya-chan...
She's gotten a lot better.
It's like someone's pulling her hands.
Hasn't she gotten a bit too good?
It's like someone's taking her away.
Daiya-chan, come back!
Yuzuka-san, she won't let go of my hands!
What?
Yuzuka-san, call for help!
Out of Range
No way, we're out of range!
Miton! Pochi-kun!
What should I do?
Transform!
Chosen ones! It's time for you to join
forces and save the captured princess!
But...
Transform!
Mafuyu-san?!
The barrier...
Transform!
Yuzuka!
Wait... The barrier...
Let's go!
Right!
We'll save you, Daiya-chan!
Time to hit the gas!
They're moving across the water!
Are they mermaids?
Yuzuka...
Daiya-chan...
Huh? My magic is...
Yuzuka...
Hurry...
Hey! What's going on?
What's happening to them?
Yuzuka's magic is...
I won't accept a bad ending like this!
Daiya-chan!
Yuzuka-chan!
To be continued!
To Be Continued