I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Before I knew it, your colors were painted across the sky
I want you to hear what I have to say
For some reason, we won't understand each other
Until that time comes
Hopefully it'll sit right with you
Unsteady times like these will go by, however
Sorry for always causing you problems
Ah, I love you
I love you
I want you to know that
I got a lot of work done today.
The sunrise, huh?
Makes me feel alive.
Dad?
Yuzuka, why are you wearing that?
I've become a magical girl!
A what?
I'm a meowgical girl too.
Magical Girl Chiya here!
The sparkle has been stolen from this world!
Sparkle?
It's here!
Adhere to the eight-hour work day!
No unpaid overtime!
What's going on?
It's stealing the sparkle from this world,
the jobs that make people feel happy to be alive!
The Emperor of Evil,
The Labor Standards Inspection Office!
What?
I'll fight, too!
Ally of the all-nighter,
Working Gold!
5,000 yen a bottle!
5,000 Yen a Bottle
As long as there is work in this world,
I will continue to work happily!
Magical Middle-aged Man: Father!
Inspection!
Watch out!
Golem, you're a bad guy
for attacking Yuzuka!
I'll help myew!
Chocolate Cookie Cluster!
Meow! Meow!
Those under 15 can only work until 8 PM.
Feel the power of rare stationery!
Inspection! Inspection! Inspection! Inspection!
Inspection, you say?!
For my beloved family,
until my very life runs out,
I will work!
Long live the Labor Standards Act!
We did it!
Sir, you're pretty ameowzing!
Now I can work all I want.
That's great, Dad.
Yeah!
I slept so well.
As long as I have my health, I can work.
And I'm in good health because I have work.
All right!
Be back later!
To be continued.
To Be Continued