I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Before I knew it, your colors were painted across the sky
I want you to hear what I have to say
For some reason, we won't understand each other
Until that time comes
Hopefully it'll sit right with you
Unsteady times like these will go by, however
Sorry for always causing you problems
Ah, I love you
I love you
I want you to know that
Transform!
This is pretty useful.
Being a magical girl isn't so bad, huh?
Hey! That's my ice cream!
I was saving it to eat with Chiya-chan later!
The chocolate ice cream was supposed to be yours.
I swear...
nothing good has come of this.
Hey, Yuzuka...
Has anything good happened
since you became a magical girl?
Anything good...
I can't think of anything.
Tsk.
Now, why would she say that?
Just being able to transform into a
magical girl should be a good thing!
I didn't expect her to think otherwise!
Well, I guess I kind of understand.
I'm saved!
It's from Mafuyu-san.
Yuzuka-san, Chiya-san,
I just got back.
Welcome back, Daiya-chan.
I guess it's pool season now, huh?
Yeah!
I'm a little bit sad I can't swim,
but I'm going to try to learn this year!
Yeah! I'm sure you'll be able to!
Thank you!
Oh, hi there, Granny.
It's pretty hot today, isn't it?
"Granny"?
Temporarily closed
This is it.
Welcome!
Hello!
Ah, it's cool in here!
Feels like heaven.
That feels so good...
AC is such a great invention.
Chocolate cigarette candy?!
Is this your parents' shop?
Close!
It's my grandfather's.
Are you closed today?
That's not it, either.
My grandfather has a guild match to
determine who'll represent Japan,
so he can't leave the computer.
That should do it.
Wait, I'm one frame too late!
I'm not going to make it!
Online games?!
He's an addict...
Anyways, I invited you here because...
Yes?
I want to show off our magic!
What?!
Transform!
To be continued.
To Be Continued