I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Before I knew it, your colors were painted across the sky
I want you to hear what I have to say
For some reason, we won't understand each other
Until that time comes
Hopefully it'll sit right with you
Unsteady times like these will go by, however
Sorry for always causing you problems
Ah, I love you
I love you
I want you to know that
It's not as if entrance exams only start
once you're in your third year.
You'll have a real advantage if you start preparing early.
I say that, but I imagine students
have lots of things to worry about.
What are you getting at?
You need a study session!
You'll get together with anything you don't understand,
and Mafuyu can tutor you.
But we're not struggling.
I see! You're not...
Not even a little?!
There's nothing I'm particularly
having trouble with in my studies.
There's no way a student like that exists!
Well, they do. That's how these girls are.
You expect me to believe that there are actually magical girls who do well in school?
Are all magical girls bad at studying?
You're late!
According to our data,
Tee Hee
Tee hee!
that's the only conclusion.
Tee Hee
I-Is that so.
That's some prejudice.
A study session?
That'd really help!
I need help with a lot of my subjects...
I thought that's what they'd say.
What should I report to Mafuyu?
You see...
They're younger than me.
I wonder if I could help them out in some way.
If you want to do something all
students do, try a study session.
A study session...
That's a good idea!
I didn't expect magical girls to actually do well in school.
I understand.
I'll help out.
I'm in your debt.
No need for that.
We're partners, aren't we?
There, there.
Miton!
You know, he could have
just asked us out for tea.
That's true. You're right!
I'm glad I asked you, Chiya!
Did you just assume that we're friends now?
I just keep quiet when Yuzuka's around.
When Yuzuka's not here,
you will address me by my surname.
I'll engrave it into my brain, Sakagami-san!
We're going out for tea?
Yes, Mafuyu-san has invited us.
On Saturday, right?
That sounds good.
I'll let her know, then.
That was easy.
This Saturday, would you like to admire
and appreciate Yuzuka with me?
Hold on a second...
Wow!
Hmm, what should I say?
I wonder what would make me sound more grown up...
She's responded.
Let me see.
I'd like to admire and appreciate
you too, Chiya-chan!
How'd I do? How'd I do?
Oh!
That is a conversation best saved for another time.
To be continued.
To Be Continued