I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Before I knew it, your colors were painted across the sky
I want you to hear what I have to say
For some reason, we won't understand each other
Until that time comes
Hopefully it'll sit right with you
Unsteady times like these will go by, however
Sorry for always causing you problems
Ah, I love you
I love you
I want you to know that
Hi there, boss kitty.
Aren't your kitty friends here today?
Kitties!
Hello!
That tickles!
Oh?
Are you alright?
M-My angel.
Daiya-chan!
Yuzuka-san!
We're headed to the café.
Would you like to come with us?
Sure.
I'll come with you.
Stop it! Stop it!
There you go.
Now you're all better.
S-So bright!
I can't look directly at her!
Blue-light-cutting glasses, equipped!
This is a wonderful café.
With the AC running,
Mr. Fallen Warrior over there
looks nice and cool, too.
Fallen warrior?
Granny, that red scarf really suits you!
Granny?!
Are you there, Granny?
It's because I've been neglecting the café!
Looks like she can see all kinds of things.
Is Daiya-chan...
No, she's not a magical girl.
She might be able to see us to some degree,
but I doubt she can hear us.
It's extremely rare, but there are people
who can see us without meeting the
requirements of a magical girl.
I think she can see too much.
Oh, Mr. Fallen Warrior.
You've cooled down plenty,
so you're ready to go back now, huh?
Farewell!
I guess he went to Heaven.
Granny...
Granny, please go to Heaven already.
What a waste!
She feels a lot more
magical girl-y than Chiya to me.
Yeah. At the very least, I don't feel
like she has any ill intentions towards us.
Gulp!
Then how about I help you
two ascend to Heaven next?
To be continued.
To Be Continued