I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Before I knew it, your colors were painted across the sky
I want you to hear what I have to say
For some reason, we won't understand each other
Until that time comes
Hopefully it'll sit right with you
Unsteady times like these will go by, however
Sorry for always causing you problems
Ah, I love you
I love you
I want you to know that
Let's play again sometime.
Thank goodness.
Was that some kind of magic trick?
I'll have to wipe your memories.
Are they really magical girls?
A girl on a dolphin saved
another girl who was drowning.
Wow, I wish I'd gotten a video of that.
Yuzuka-san...
If Miton had died before the magic was dispelled,
what would have happened
to Yuzuka's transformation?
Maybe she would've ended up naked?
Looks like you're awake.
Um, where's Yuzuka-san?
Over there.
Is she taking a sand bath?
It was just sort of an impulse.
And as a reward, we gave her extra sand.
Oh, so you're alive.
Apparently I fell into a deep sleep.
It's like I died and came back to life! I feel great...
What's this?
Yeah, that's plenty.
Compact
You can sleep forever!
After that, I quickly recovered
You can do it!
Loosen up a little.
and had fun with everyone in the ocean.
Almost there.
You did it!
You made it five meters.
And Daiya-chan got a little
better at swimming, too.
This isn't enough firepower
to defeat the zombies!
I curse you!
You must be tired after today.
You should get some sleep.
About your question yesterday...
When you asked if I was happy I became a magical girl.
Yeah...
I was able to save Daiya-chan,
got to be closer friends with Chiya-chan,
and became friends with
Mafuyu-san and Pochi-san.
I'm glad I became a magical girl.
I see.
Daiya, Mafuyu, Pochi, and Chiya...
what about me?
Well, you're...
That's it.
Huh? What was that?
It's time for work.
Fireworks!
Feels like summer.
Isn't it beautiful,
Chiya-chan, Mafuyu-san, Daiya-chan?
The end.
The End