I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Before I knew it, your colors were painted across the sky
I want you to hear what I have to say
For some reason, we won't understand each other
Until that time comes
Hopefully it'll sit right with you
Unsteady times like these will go by, however
Sorry for always causing you problems
Ah, I love you
I love you
I want you to know that
Yuzuka wakes up at six every morning.
Good morning.
She pays attention in class
and has excellent grades.
She carries out all of her chores perfectly.
She refuses to take a bath with me.
Honestly, it's absolutely ridiculous
for a magical girl not to do so.
She doesn't like being a magical girl.
She's an unusual magical girl.
Hey, Yuzuka.
Yes?
Are you happy you became a magical girl?
Are you ignoring me?
Are you?
The... beach?
One of my father's friends
invited me to their beach house.
Would you like to come with me?
A beach house, huh?
Sounds great!
It is!
This is it.
That's a private beach!
That's more than just a house.
Apparently only people staying
at the hotel there can visit.
The beach...
Let's go, Yuzuka-chan!
Let's have an adventure!
Let's go, Yuzuka.
We can make great summer memories.
S-Sure.
Yay!
It's the beach!
The blue is so deep, it could suck you in!
Why does Shiori-chan have a bomb on her, too?
So hot...
Sorry I took so long.
I knew it.
You should have just
transformed into your swimsuit.
I don't really...
Though your school swimsuit is nice, too.
Pretty stimulating in itself.
Mafuyu-san!
Can't say I disagree.
Not you too, Chiya-chan!
A little more to the right.
That's good.
To the right. Right.
That's good!
You can do it!
Strike!
You've gotten pretty good.
Thank you.
Hey!
Yuzuka-chan, you should swim with us, too!
She's a tough one to crack.
It'd be a good chance for her to get used to her swimsuit, too.
Guess we'll just have to drag her out here.
I get to be the one to take off her jacket.
Huh? What's up?
Okay, I'm coming.
To Be Continued
To be continued!