I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Before I knew it, your colors were painted across the sky
I want you to hear what I have to say
For some reason, we won't understand each other
Until that time comes
Hopefully it'll sit right with you
Unsteady times like these will go by, however
Sorry for always causing you problems
Ah, I love you
I love you
I want you to know that
Chiya-chan's going to...
be a magical girl!?
Magical Miracle Chronicle!
Lovelin, Goblin.
Debauchery abound!
Magical Girl Chiya appears!
Underestimate me,
and you'll go up in flames.
Bang!
How cool!
With all of us...
working together...
Here I go!
There!
...we'll make this world into a Chiya-ry fairy tale!
It's pretty, isn't it?
Chiya-chan.
Mafuyu-san.
That's not happening.
I was wondering what you were going on about.
In the first place, Mafuyu's retirement and
my next assignment are two separate issues.
B-Besides, Mafuyu isn't going
to retire anytime soon.
We should just have fun for now.
Of course!
I'm going to have as much fun as possible
messing with both
Yuzuka-chan and Chiya-chan.
You're going to have fun...
messing with us?
What are you planning on doing
after you graduate from high school?
I'm thinking about helping with the shop.
Then I can just take over at some point.
Take over?
Then I can spend all day playing games.
Viva my second life.
You heard him.
He really is a waste of air.
We had the shop all to ourselves.
For a weird reason, though.
Hi, everyone!
Daiya-chan, are you running errands?
Yes.
My father is coming home from being at sea for the first time in a year.
So my mom said she'd make us a feast.
Yay!
Y-Yay...?
Well, I must be on my way.
See you later.
Oh, one thing did happen.
Something good, I mean.
Has anything good happened to you
since you became a magical girl?
I'm not sure if has much to do with being
a magical girl, but since Miton came...
What is it?
My father comes home late,
and I used to eat dinner alone,
so it's kind of nice that Miton
enjoys eating my cooking so much.
Yuzuka...
That's because your cooking
is so much better than the
literal garbage I was eating.
He had that coming.
Forget it! Nothing good has come of this at all!
To be continued!
To Be Continued