I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Let's raise our banners and march in a dream-colored parade
Answering our own curiosity of what's up ahead with our own hands
Marching across the town to the beat of our excited hearts
We'll continue onward and chase those balloons ahead!
Hey, what do you think's next?
School, huh?
Are you really coming with me?
Of course I am!
Don't worry.
Normal people can neither hear, nor see me.
You were alone for breakfast again.
Where's your father?
Everyday, he rides the first train to work and comes back on the last.
Does he work in a sweatshop?!
I've asked him about that before...
Yuzuka, a sweatshop is a bad place that works people like slaves.
I'm doing my work because I like it,
and I'm getting paid properly.
So please don't call it a sweatshop.
He's the definition of a corporate slave!
Morning, Daiya-chan.
Oh, Yuzuka-san.
Good morning.
What a cute cat!
Yeah!
Cuddling him feels so nice.
See you later.
Bye! Have a good day!
School Route
Morning...
Good morning!
School Route
Wh-What's wrong?
Nothing.
Hey, Yuzuka.
Yes?
You and I are friends, right?
I believe so...
Has anything been bothering you recently?
No, not really.
Then...
You don't have to answer if you don't want to, but...
Yeah?
What is that creature?
She can see him!
She can see me!
M-My name is Miton.
I'm Yuzuka's partner.
He's not my partner.
Let me explain!
Yuzuka is a very dear friend of mine.
Don't call yourself her partner without my permission.
I'm sorry.
I guess other people really can't see him.
Only those who have the ability to become magical girls can see me.
You can have one of my octopus wieners.
Thanks!
I want to see you transform.
I guess most people would...
Let her see.
Miton-san?
You're friends, right?
What's...
Chiya-chan.
Transform.
Wh-What do you think?
It's cute.
Sakagami Chiya.
I'm Miton.
I won't let you do this without me.
Let me in on it.
G-Gladly.
To be continued!
To Be Continued