I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Let's raise our banners and march in a dream-colored parade
Answering our own curiosity of what's up ahead with our own hands
Marching across the town to the beat of our excited hearts
We'll continue onward and chase those balloons ahead!
Hey, what do you think's next?
Yuzuka...
I'm off to work.
Your dad's going to do what he always does...
Have fun working 21 hours straight,
from the first train of the day to the last!
Good morning...
Time to eat.
Good morning, Yuzuka-san!
Good morning, Daiya-chan.
What wonderful weather.
It's going to be a great day.
I can't wait to get it started!
Did you do the math homework?
Yep, all of it.
It was pretty easy, huh?
Yeah.
It was mostly just a review.
Huh?
It's nothing.
You just had something on your face.
Did I?
Thanks.
Let's go.
Yeah.
You can see me?
You can see me!
You can't fly?
Don't be afraid, I mean you no harm.
I was just setting up a barrier.
Now no one will interrupt us.
A barrier?
Normal humans can't see or hear me.
The fact that you can means you have what it takes to be a magical girl!
A-A magical girl?!
My name is Miton.
I-I'm Hanami Yuzuka.
Okay, Yuzuka, try transforming!
What?
If you focus on that bracelet and shout "Transform,"
you'll turn into a magical girl!
A magical girl...
Get him, Mr. Carrot!
Transform!
Why is it a swimsuit?
That's my line! You tell me!
The magical girl outfit takes on the form that best suits its wearer.
I guess a swimsuit is what suits you best...
Stare...
How can you say that while ogling me like that?!
Turn me back!
You'll turn back if you touch the bracelet and say, "Release."
Release.
Well, you'll get used to it in no time.
I don't want to!
Well, at least swimsuits are good for the summer.
Nice to meet you, Yuzuka.
No way! I don't want to wear that thing!
Take off this bracelet...
Smelly
You stink!
You smell like garbage!
To be continued!
To Be Continued