I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Let's raise our banners and march in a dream-colored parade
Answering our own curiosity of what's up ahead with our own hands
Marching across the town to the beat of our excited hearts
We'll continue onward and chase those balloons ahead!
Hey, what do you think's next?
Transform.
So I still transform, even if I just whisper it.
My power is water magic...
I can use it to create water.
I'm also able to control it.
I wonder if gravity doesn't affect it?
I can control water, but only if I create it.
A chick!
Time for a walk.
It's an amazing ability, but...
I have to wear this swimsuit to use it.
Why is this part open in the front?
Yuzuka.
Yes?
Swimsuits are meant to be worn in the pool, not the bathtub.
You were watching me?
Of course not.
The bracelet tells me when you transform, though.
The bath...
I guess some people wear them at mixed baths.
But this is my house.
Then why?
I just wanted to try out my magic.
I see.
Then you could have just transformed here.
But I...
don't want to
do it here!
That's why I
used the bath!
What is it?
I'm mad!
I... I see that.
I don't like how I wear a swimsuit when I transform.
H-Huh?
It's weird having strangers look at me when I'm the only one wearing one.
R-Right...
But I'm the one who made you into a magical girl, right?
Yes.
So we're like partners...
You're a stranger.
No, no, no, no, no. I'm just—
Right.
To Be Continued
To be continued!