I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Let's raise our banners and march in a dream-colored parade
Answering our own curiosity of what's up ahead with our own hands
Marching across the town to the beat of our excited hearts
We'll continue onward and chase those balloons ahead!
Hey, what do you think's next?
Transform!
So yours is a swimsuit! How cute!
Yours is cute too, Shinogi-san.
Just call me Mafuyu.
I actually really like mine.
But I'm really happy.
Pochi-kun said...
There's no longer a need for magical girls.
I imagine the chances of another one appearing are incredibly low.
That really got me worried.
I thought I was the only magical girl.
Well, the system that—
So, anyway...
She shut him up!
Would you be my friends?
Thanks.
Who knew there'd be another one so close by?
Sure.
It's a pleasure.
We can't sense each other anymore.
Want to link up again?
No, thanks.
I'm surprised, though.
I didn't think you'd be with a magical girl.
You wouldn't understand.
With no roof over my head, all I could do was sort through trash left by humans. Life was miserable.
I know that feel!
Do you two go to the same school?
Yeah.
We're second years in middle school.
I see.
You're younger than me, then.
What grade are you in, Shinogi-san?
I said to just call me Mafuyu.
I'm a third year.
So I'll be retiring soon.
Retiring?
I guess it would be rude to ask about it.
When will that be?
Well, I'll keep that a secret for now.
Oh, yeah... Where are Pochi and Miton?
My friend!
They've sure gotten closer...
I didn't see anything.
You're ignoring it?!
We should get going, Mafuyu.
Why? I want to talk some more!
We're running out of time.
You were going to buy new
school supplies today, right?
Yeah, but...
So we need to be going.
Let's make time to talk on some other day.
Yeah.
Good point.
The stores will be closing soon.
You don't have a stationery store near your house?
This is the only place that sells 0.4mm lead.
Déjà vu!
That's right. This is the only place you can buy it.
0.4mm.
Sakagami-san, you also...
Please call me Chiya.
0.3mm is just too thin for me.
I know, right?
They've sure gotten closer...
To be continued!
To Be Continued