I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Let's raise our banners and march in a dream-colored parade
Answering our own curiosity of what's up ahead with our own hands
Marching across the town to the beat of our excited hearts
We'll continue onward and chase those balloons ahead!
Hey, what do you think's next?
My dad says he'll be home early.
Oh? That doesn't happen often.
Normal people can't see you, right, Miton?
Yeah.
Can you make yourself visible to them?
That would do more harm than good.
But I want my mom and dad to know—
I'd have to manipulate their memories to do it.
Manipulate their memories?
I can't risk having people know of my existence.
If it were to spread around,
there's a good chance I'd end up the subject of some organization's experiments.
Noooo!
I didn't think about that.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
It makes sense that you don't want to hide things from your family.
I just thought if they knew about you,
it'd be easier to get food money from them.
Food money?!
I'd like to treat you to luxurious things now and then...
Luxury
But I guess you're right.
Yuzuka...
It's not good to hide things from your family.
You're drooling.
Hanami
I'm home.
You're back early.
One of my coworkers got sick,
so I was able to come home after stopping by to check on him.
Dad...
Hm? What is it?
Do you like pets?
You want one?
Well...
Yes, we can get one.
Thank you!
So what do you want?
A dog? A cat?
Actually...
What is that creature?
Transform!
Strong magic is required
for the memory manipulation.
I'll need you to transform.
Yuzuka...
Miton!
You're back early.
I was able to come home after stopping by to check on him.
Do you like pets?
Yes, we can get one.
Thank you!
So what do you want?
A dog? A cat?
Actually...
It's huge!
That's one... fat... parrot...
Once he wakes up, he should see me as a parrot.
A parrot...
I also restored his stamina.
Still, I've never seen anyone so exhausted.
Is employee labor even tougher than magical girl battles?
I'm also kind of...
Because you've depleted your magic.
Dad?
Sorry, did I wake you?
No.
Is it almost time for the first train?
Yeah.
I slept really well.
My body feels so light!
I think I could work for 200 hours straight.
Please don't!
To Be Continued
To be continued!