I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Let's raise our banners and march in a dream-colored parade
Answering our own curiosity of what's up ahead with our own hands
Marching across the town to the beat of our excited hearts
We'll continue onward and chase those balloons ahead!
Hey, what do you think's next?
So cute!
I'm here.
Hi there, Sakagami-san.
I ran into her on my way here.
She said she wanted to come along.
Yeah!
Um...
Am I in the way?
Squee!
W-Would you like some ice cream?
My treat.
Really? Thank you very much!
Squee!
Here you go.
This is so good!
Rum raisin... Chocolate mint... Raspberry...
Hey, why don't we take some pictures together?
It's my first time in one of these.
Mine, too.
Come in closer.
Say cheese!
BFFS
Well, I have a curfew, so I'd better get going now.
I had a lot of fun.
Okay. See you later, Daiya-chan.
She's a nice girl.
Well, shall we?
Thank you for your business!
You always get your stationery here.
Is this your favorite store?
No.
This is the only place that sells 0.4mm lead.
That's rare!
A penguin?!
Hey, Pochi-kun...
My name isn't Pochi.
Is that...
Yeah, he's the same as me.
Good to see you're doing well, "Pochi-kun."
PFFT
Miton, you jerk!
If you're with a thing that's like Pochi-kun...
You must be a magical girl!
Nope.
Huh?
This one is my best friend.
We're not best friends.
She doesn't even like you.
I'm sorry for the mix-up.
My name is Shinogi Mafuyu.
And this is Pochi-kun.
My name isn't Pochi.
My name is Pokenchiss Dil Prafsolaf—
Just call him Pochi-kun.
PFFT
My name is Sakagami Chiya.
This is Hanami Yuzuka.
This thing is Miton.
"Thing"?
Shinogi-san, was it?
Just call me Mafuyu.
Y-You're a magical girl, right?
Yep, I'm a magical girl.
And, um... Hanami-san,
you're a magical girl too, right?
Um...
That's right.
Yuzuka is a magical girl, and Chiya—
TSK
Sakagami-san has what it takes to be one.
I see.
So that's why she can see m—
Well, anyway, that aside...
She ignored him.
I was ignored.
I'm happy there's another
magical girl around besides me!
Another magical girl...
A new... friend.
To be continued!
To Be Continued