I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Let's raise our banners and march in a dream-colored parade
Answering our own curiosity of what's up ahead with our own hands
Marching across the town to the beat of our excited hearts
We'll continue onward and chase those balloons ahead!
Hey, what do you think's next?
Right now, Yuzuka is focusing on her studies at school.
Her grades are excellent,
but her family isn't around much.
Her dad works too hard, and her mom is extremely laid-back, and they all seem to get along just fine.
But...
Yuzuka.
Yes?
Do you not have many friends?
Not Many Friends
Not
Many
Friends
Not
Many
Friends
Not
Many
Friends
Not
Many
Friends
Not
Many
Friends
Not... many... friends...
Let... Let me think about it for a second.
Huh?
My friends...
Yuzuka.
There's Chiya-chan and...
Chiya-chan and...
Yuzuka.
Um...
Who else?
Hello!
Cuddling him feels so nice.
Oh, Daiya-chan!
Yeah.
Age doesn't matter when it comes to friends.
Also...
Would you be my friends?
Shinogi-san!
We even said out loud that we'd be friends!
Also...
Also... Also...
Other friends...
I have either a few or a lot
depending on your definition of "friend"!
Huh? What do you mean?
The people I always hang out with are my friends, of course,
Classmates and such
but there are other people I know and like.
People like that can be called friends, too.
Classmates and such
I see.
Do you think having a lot of friends is normal?
But...
The more friends you have, the weaker your bonds with each one of them will be!
And wouldn't you agree that isn't a good thing?
I... I guess...
I get it!
You're embarrassed that you don't have many friends.
Th-That's not it!
I just think quality is more important than quantity!
I see.
I guess I didn't phrase it properly.
Ahem...
Is Chiya your only friend at school?
Oh, for crying out loud!
So that's what happened.
And then?
What did she say?
She put on what looked to be a smile.
I see.
Do you have any last requests?
That's the same look!
I know you're just trying to look out for her,
but you should really save that for after she considers you a friend.
One of her friends...
Yuzuka, I've decided.
Decided what?
I'm...
going to be your best friend!
The End
The end!