I've Had Enough of Being a Magical Girl.
Let's raise our banners and march in a dream-colored parade
Answering our own curiosity of what's up ahead with our own hands
Marching across the town to the beat of our excited hearts
We'll continue onward and chase those balloons ahead!
Hey, what do you think's next?
Doing homework?
The answer to 1 is "c = 32."
You got it in one second?!
I let my calculation chip do the math.
That's not fair.
I'm impressed that you actually do your homework.
I think it's normal to do your homework.
Come on! What's wrong with you?!
You're supposed to let it pile up, get in trouble, and then have a sleepover to finish it all up.
Sleepover
That's how I thought it worked.
What type of magical girls
have you dealt with before?
You can cook, you're good with your studies, and you're cute.
You're the perfect woman.
Isn't there anything you're bad at?
Or anything you don't like doing?
Something I'm bad at?
Well...
I'm bad at breaking chopsticks apart.
I'm also not good at opening bags of chips.
That's not what I meant.
Like, something you physically can't handle.
Oh, in that case...
What is it?
When you... sexually harass me.
Okay, let's forget that.
What about things you don't like doing?
Given your age, the typical answer would be studying, but...
Well...
Transforming.
You really don't like that swimsuit, do you?
All right. I'll see what I can do about the system.
What? You can do that?
Why didn't you do that sooner?
Well, if I look into it, it's possible we could get rid of the swimsuit altogether...
Th-Then...
...leaving you naked!
Ow! Stop! Not there!
YEOW!
YEEK!
That brush is so scary...
Could I transform, and then just go about my life like normal?
Like normal?
Yes.
If I transform, I'll end up in that swimsuit,
but if I take it off right afterwards and put on other clothes, I don't think it'd be a problem.
Changing
I'm starting to take pity on that swimsuit...
But that might be difficult.
Just maintaining the transformation depletes your magic.
And if you lose consciousness, you'll revert back.
I see...
Then I guess I'll just have to wear something over the swimsuit.
I wonder why that swimsuit was chosen as the best outfit for you, considering you hate it so much.
But if you wear clothes over the swimsuit,
if we consider what happened the other day,
I think it's highly possible that some problem will occur when you revert back.
Still, shall we give it a try?
I'll try it on my own!
No Mitons Allowed!
-Yuzuka
Transform.
Yuzuka...
M-Mom?!
To be continued!
To Be Continued