What's going on?!
The year is 2016 AD.
The world of slightly clumsy, cheeky, tomboyish,
panicky high school girl Asagaya Minoa is in crisis.
A true madame and anime otaku, Kamiigusa Alice.
A studious glasses-wearing girl and anime otaku, Kouenji Miko.
Cosplayer and anime otaku, Aoyama Erica.
Evil-eyed man with special abilities,
and anime otaku, Musashisakai Kai...
Her comrades were all consumed by anime.
Her bittersweet but burning relationship with cowardly traitor Nakano Aurora is concluded.
Aurora reveals many truths:
That the anime world and
real world exist in parallel—
that the anime club was the location
of Japan's first anime studio—
and that Aurora himself was a
resident of the anime world.
Minoa can be heard shouting far and wide.
"Aurora-senpai!"
Did that revelation ever happen?
Did they just kill me off?!
Would you please stop calling me Aurora?
And what do you mean by
"cheeky, tomboyish, and panicky"?
Minoa's protest against her character
profile was shot down without mercy.
You're going to ignore me?
This man with the anime world beret
is the man who attempted to claim this program's setting as his own.
But to do so, he would have
needed to be far more capable.
As a result, he was rejected by both anime and reality.
His very existence was erased.
Death by narrator?
No!
What about our promise?
What did you promise?
My name...
That he would change my name.
Maybe he's already fulfilled his promise.
That's it.
That must be it!
My name is...
Aurora.
Son of a bitch!
Where's the beret?
Neko-senpai, I still can't believe it.
Isn't anime something that people make?
That's where you're mistaken.
You didn't create us.
We've always existed.
You only merely depicted us.
I've watched it happen.
Anime is created into this world, and is spread.
It took decades.
You're becoming anime, too.
But first...
Do something about my damn name!
Aurora.
Stop!
Aurora!
Quit harmonizing my name!
Minoa.
What's the matter? You're so out of it.
Have you watched yesterday's Mahojuku?
The art was amazing.
I wish I could have highlights like
hers in my eyes in my close-up shots.
I want them to do my hair gradients, too.
I totally agree.
That studio really brings out the actors' strengths.
Indeed.
Thank goodness.
We still have time to make changes.
It must have been a dream.
We do.
Totally.
Hey!
I'll write the script from here.
It's time to start class!
Nice!
You there! Get back to your seats!
Is that how it is?
I'll make it even better.
Awesome!
What?
What was that?
Are you serious?!
It looks like the robotics club
botched its new weapon again.
What do you mean, "again"?
What's the matter?
Minoacchi.
What's wrong with you?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
Have you acquired a new element?
Alice-chan, call Sebas-san, please.
Sebas?
Why?
Just do it.
It's a mask!
Half-assed.
Mon petit coeur.
I wasn't dreaming.
I thought we had you.
Minoa, why're you running away?
I thought we were friends?!
We have a club meeting at lunch, Minoacchi.
So, Dad, your recommendation for
the season is Yoyoyo Season 2?
Onee-chan?
Absolutely.
Your Reindeer in August is my favorite returning series.
That's not bad, either.
I have high hopes for Papipupepopip, too.
It's extended.
No way!
Hey, welcome home.
Mom.
I never knew Dad had the day off.
You come home early when you
don't have club work, huh?
Yeah, and we only had morning classes.
I didn't have much to do.
What's your favorite this season?
I can't wait for A Sister's All You Need.
Miyako-chan's absolutely adorable.
I know, totally!
I've been interested in that one, too.
I'm here, you know.
Mom, can my friends stay over
in the traditional room upstairs?
Can't you use your own room?
I'm having three over.
Just don't break my figures, okay?
Let it consume you.
Death by
Narrator
Let it consume you!
Just let anime consume you.
Like everyone else.
Like everyone else?
That's right. Nothing will change.
The world won't disappear.
I won't become a zombie.
You'll stop being lonely.
This is how it should be, right?
Why do you look so sad?
Hurry up.
Become one with that girl.
The door to the new world is almost open.
Come to our side, Minoa.
It was fun.
I thought Alice-chan and Miko-chan were
unapproachable, but I got to talk to them.
About anime.
We decided to make the anime club together,
and we met Erica-senpai,
Kaikai-senpai and Aurora-senpai.
We always had anime to talk about.
I don't want everyone to leave me.
So let's just become anime.
No.
Ow...
Now you're getting it, Maya.
I know.
What's going on?!
Got some time, little kitten?
Neko-senpai!
Mrowr.
Meow.
Now, are you ready?
Let's run.
Meowky!
You've rejected becoming an anime.
You're gonna be rejected too.
Rejected?
You'll stop existing in this world.
Is there no way to change things back to normal?
We just need the beret.
What's the deal with that beret?
It's the source of great power,
connecting the anime world to the real world.
I found it!
At last, I'm...
We just need to bring the beret from the
border between worlds back to the anime world.
At least, that's my guess.
What border?
It's the door in the club room. What else?
How did this happen in the first place?
Long story short...
Minoa's
world
What's inside
here?
Desire to open
the door
Border
Woo!
High-school girl's voice!
It's been a while!
Desire to get a
look at the
high-school girl
Coincidence!
Just a peek!!
In retrospect, this was a
big bang-level bad move.
Neko Excitement Gauge
Anime world
It's like this.
So it's all your fault!
You're unbelievable.
You know, though, this all happened
because you let Aurora get in your head,
and you opened the door.
Jeez!
You're going to blame me?
Something's coming.
Anime-Gataris
The eyecatch...
No!
Anime-Gataris
Minoa,
Katharsis
That was terrible.
I didn't expect the eyecatch.
What is this?
The beret has begun purifying the world.
It's all becoming a blank slate.
A blank slate?
It's going to be erased.
This is bad!
It's all too late.
I had a fun life.
Wait, wait, wait!
Hey! Get a grip!
You're being consumed by a recap episode!
You're determined to take
back your world, aren't you?
My world?
The world that's vanishing now is full of your memories and your friends.
I won't let them erase my world!
That's it!
Your paw is so squishy.
It gets me any she-cat, every time.
Let's go.
Hurry!
It's catching up!
What the heck?!
It's trying to remove impurities.
Is there no one on my side?
Sure there is.
Minoa.
You're from Ultra Katharsis Koritsi.
No way!
The robot's coming!
You have allies in the anime world.
All the anime you've cherished.
It's so stiff.
Go, damn it!
It's the real thing!
Oh no, I'm getting nervous.
I appreciate your feelings,
but pull the damn throttle.
Oh, right.
Move... Move!
Go!
Listen to my song!
Get them!
Eternal Symphony!
Damn, that's as far as we go.
I'm going to ram through...
with my drill that pierces the heavens!
Go!
Katharsis!
We did it!
Where am I?
What's going on?
Isn't this the climax?
We went against this world.
We've been erased.
No...
Mikene-chan!
Aurora-senpai?
Mikene-chan, he's calling you.
You're Mikene-chan.
I'm Minoa!
Main characters
"You're sorely mistaken
if you think twin tails
are all tsundere!"
Kandaiji Saaya
Twin tail blonde princess-type.
Secretly an anime otaku,
but it's totally obvious.
Takes the story in an
unimaginable direction.
Moe Character
Protagonist
Light Novel Type
Moe Character
"I watch lots of anime.
I recently watched Gh**li!"
Yotsugi Mikene
First-year high school student.
Has an anime otaku sister,
but is herself an anime newbie.
Protagonist
"This world in which I exist
is not the true world."
Azusawa Najimi
A seemingly bland girl
who actually has huge boobs.
Loves alternate world light novels.
Shuts herself inside her own world
with her obscure knowledge.
Light Novel Type
This is bad,
we're back to the planning phase.
That's a terrible name, even in planning!
Nothing changes, even when I wear this.
We can't make use of that.
Wear it for me, Mikene-chan!
It's Minoa.
With this hat, one can do anything.
It's a symbol of absolute status and power.
No.
The person who wore this
never thought such a thing.
This hat is a symbol of dreams,
aspirations, and passion.
It's the bridge between our world and the anime world.
All right.
So first, do something about my name!
This kid totally doesn't get it.
Open a path to the border.
Guys...
Come over here.
We're all going to vanish
if we don't do something.
Anime won't disappear.
You're just being stubborn, Minoa.
Join our family so that we may live on together.
Don't oppose anime.
I love anime.
I absolutely love it now.
I was introduced to all kinds of things
by talking about anime with you.
And it made us friends.
Alice-chan, you invited me to the anime club.
You opened the door to anime for me.
That's where it all began.
Miko-chan, you never gave up, no matter
how many times the scenario got scrapped.
You showed me the passion and
perseverance it takes to make anime.
Erica-senpai, you taught me how fun
and amazing Akihabara and events are.
You taught me to truly enjoy myself.
Kaikai-senpai, you saved the anime club
from its first crisis with your powerful speech.
It's Kai.
I love anime.
Anime brought me together with all of you.
I adore it.
But in this anime, my favorite
people are disappearing.
I hate this piece of shit anime!
Mi... no... a...
Wait!
Alice...
It's over.
My name...
Aurora-senpai!
Don't call me that!
You helped me a lot.
You always kept me from giving up.
I admire you, Aurora-senpai.
I'm not giving up.
No...
It's over?
Alice-chan?
Hold on tight!
Guys... Why?
There's still a lot of anime we need to talk about.
Alice...
We haven't finished talking.
Your passionate speech really did it.
I wouldn't mind appreciating you.
We all appreciate you.
Let's chat some more, Minoa.
And more, and more, and lots more!
But we have to take this beret
to the other side of the door.
How do we do that?
You're kidding me!
AliceRobo?!
It's answered my summoning and
came from distant dimensions.
The art's still shoddy.
This is an exciting twist, don't you think?
Here we go, guys.
Alpha!
Not enough money.
Oh, dear.
Alice-chan!
Don't try to solve everything with money.
What else do we solve it with?
With our...
passion!
The rocket punch is the highlight of anime!
The border's opened!
Neko-senpai?
I'm sick of chasing this damn hat!
Aurora-senpai!
I want to change that name.
But you said you admire me, Minoa-chan.
I don't want to become shit anime, either.
We're taking this situation to
our side along with this beret.
But then...
Senpai!
Later, Asagaya Minoa.
Let's meet again someday
under happier circumstances.
Aurora-senpai!
Auroracchi!
Aurora!
I told you, I don't like that name.
Oh, shit! My name!
Change my name!
What?
Err...
G-G-G-Grovelboy!
Grovel?!
Senpai!
Have you still not chosen a club, Mii-chan?
Mm... not yet.
I personally like Hero School
and Roux:ZERO this season.
I have big hopes for Shikabari,
the original anime, too.
The Time Travel Shounen OP is mad legit, too,
with Jun-nii's stylish fence jump!
You sure do like anime, Minoa.
This season's kinda lopsided too, honestly.
You like anime?
Yeah.
Actually, I love it.
I do, too.
Really?
I absolutely love Director Ogikubo.
You totally get it, Alice-chan.
What's all this fuss about?
Sorry, we got carried away.
If you want to talk about anime so much,
why don't you join the Anime Club?
Anime Club?
The president's a bit weird, though.
Our Anime Club is good.
Wait, President!
Pardon us.
Here we are.
Pardon me.
Miko-chan?
I knew you'd come.
So you did like anime.
Are you looking to join?
Welcome to the Anime Club.
Mikocchi, can you redo this script? Thanks.
More changes?
I'm looking forward to it, chan-Miko.
Is that a character for
the school festival anime?
Something like that.
He's a singing, dancing
idol-lover with special powers.
What's in there?
Why don't you open it?
Look!
It's a mountain of treasures!
Nani wo shitete mo taikutsu na every day
No matter what I did, I found every day boring
Usage of Gymnasium Permit
Kokoro odoru you na tokimeki sagashiteta
I searched for something to make my heart dance
Usage of Gymnasium Permit
Shiranakatta yo kimi ni deau made
Until I met you, I never knew
Mahou mitai ni hirogaru brand new world
of this brand new world that unfolds like magic
Oshiete
So, tell me
Kimi to boku no aikotoba
our secret password
Tsunagaru tsunagaru
It'll connect us
Yuuki wo dashite
so let it be your courage
(Kouki)
Aurora
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can be even stronger
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru yo
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Boku ni wa nai kimi aru mono
As you complement and complete me
Awasareba saikyou ni!
I become the best I can be!
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can shine even brighter
Kira kira ni kagayaku no
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Kimi no "suki" boku no "suki" ga
Mixing your love with my love
Majiwareba saikou ni!
brings out the best in me!
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
The
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
The
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
End
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
End
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
What?
Are we seriously doing this?
Who does this after the heartwarming finale?!
After that ending?!
Oh, whatever.
Merry Christmas, everyone!
And next week, happy New Year.
Thanks for watching