Closing Ceremony at 9
in the auditorium
All the characters in that Dub Tone show
you recommended are so cute, Alice-chan!
I liked the story in that Sweetness and Champion
show Erica-senpai told me about.
Speaking of story, that show Ange Visual
Miko-chan wanted me to see was good, too.
You're all about anime these days.
So will you be watching anime
all through summer break, too?
That's exactly what I plan to do!
That's not all we're doing this summer, though.
You-know-what is coming up.
Yes.
You-know-what.
That-which-must-not-be-named?
Nani wo shitete mo taikutsu na every day
No matter what I did, I found every day boring
Kokoro odoru you na tokimeki sagashiteta
I searched for something to make my heart dance
Shiranakatta yo kimi ni deau made
Until I met you, I never knew
Mahou mitai ni hirogaru brand new world
of this brand new world that unfolds like magic
Oshiete
So, tell me
Kimi to boku no aikotoba
our secret password
Tsunagaru tsunagaru
It'll connect us
Yuuki wo dashite
so let it be your courage
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can be even stronger
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru yo
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Boku ni wa nai kimi aru mono
As you complement and complete me
Awasareba saikyou ni!
I become the best I can be!
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can shine even brighter
Kira kira ni kagayaku no
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Kimi no "suki" boku no "suki" ga
Mixing your love with my love
Majiwareba saikou ni!
brings out the best in me!
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
About our plans for summer break...
We're all going to you-know-what, right?
You mean it, correct?
The thing by the sea.
The mid-summer ceremony.
Or shall we call it the festival of desire?
Um, sorry, but what are you talking about?
What's this?
They're catalogs for the event.
Read this for details.
Do I have to read all of this?
Reading all of the catalogs
is a classic otaku pastime.
Nah, that's a bit of a stretch.
Just read the parts that are bookmarked.
Don't you worry, I'll give
you all the support you need.
"Notes on entering:
Wait in the entry line until the venue is open.
Nearby transit facilities will be"...
Yes?
I brought you some watermelon.
Oh, you're studying.
Yeah, studying.
Hey, Onee-chan, do we have folding chairs?
Like the ones you use outdoors?
Yeah.
We need some for our club.
Are you going camping or something?
Well...
The thing by the sea.
We're going to an event at the sea.
Huh, a sea festival or something?
So around Odaiba, then?
Yeah, that's it.
There's gonna be a ton of people there.
Wow, the anime club does those
kinds of events too, huh?
Alice-chan told me we should have
folding chairs for when we're waiting.
I see.
I think they're in the closet.
I'll get them for you later.
Thanks, Onee-chan.
Hey, camping?
No. Mii-chan's going to a sea festival
at Odaiba with her anime club people.
Wow.
She seems to be having fun
every day with her new friends.
You're up early.
I have to be on the first train
in order to make it, apparently.
Huh?
Dad's out?
Yeah, he said he's meeting up
with his friends by the sea.
Okay, see you.
See you later.
There's no one around at this time of the day.
Hey.
Neko-senpai!
Don't scare me like that.
It's on today, isn't it?
Yes.
Allow me to give you a word of warning.
The train for Ikebukuro is arriving at platform 1.
When at war, the first to
lower their guard is the first to die.
Remember that.
At war? It's not that big of a deal.
I can't breathe!
E-Excuse me.
Sorry.
Pardon me, coming through.
Please, sorry, coming through.
Over here, Minoa!
I thought I was going to die.
The train was packed, wasn't it?
It's just like the train to school, is it?
Minoa, don't let your guard down—you'll die.
It beckons me... my precious,
also known as merchandise.
It beckons me!
Musashisakai-senpai, you're way too hyper.
All right, let's get going.
Do you have your sports drink, Minoa?
Yeah.
It's important to avoid heat stroke.
Right?
I don't think that'll be enough.
What do you think this is?
This is a battlefield!
You may want to buy some more.
I'll go buy some at the
convenience store there, then.
I'll go with her—I'll worry if she's on her own.
O-Oh, no! I can't make it to the shelves.
That won't be an issue.
Miko-chan.
Kamiigusa Alice is here, Ariake!
You're so hyped up, Alicecchi.
You won't last the day.
I-I know.
But I'm just so excited.
Right, Minoa?
Yeah!
Okay,  let's go.
Isn't the venue over there?
Not so fast.
You can't get in without lining up.
Minoa.
S-Sorry.
It was an early morning.
I know, you'd only ever be up so early
during summer break for the Sunday Morning.
The Sunday Morning?
He's talking about anime and tokusatsu
shows that air on Sunday mornings.
Oh, like PreFae.
Sunday Morning has had children's
shows since long before PreFae.
It's a historically rich time period.
That's not all.
The many tokusatsu shows that set
young boys' hearts ablaze
are part of the Sunday Morning!
Well, we're the anime club, though,
so setting aside tokusatsu shows...
Don't expect to see anything but kids' shows.
There's plenty of carefully-made anime
that captivate us anime otaku, too.
There've been depictions of girls'
friendships that had me bawling.
And then there are the heartrending scenes
where the good-looking bad guy falls.
The ending dances get a lot of
attention on PreFae too, don't they?
They often have idol
choreographers working on them.
I knew about PreFae, but I
never knew it was that amazing.
There are some amazing action episodes, too.
Indeed!
There are creators who get their breaks with
their amazing Sunday morning anime battle art.
You get so excited when we're
talking about battles, Kaikai.
It's Kai!
Do any of you need to go to the washroom?
I'm still fine.
We should go while we're still fine.
It's an iron-clad rule, Alicecchi.
O-Of course.
Well, then...
I think I'll go too, then.
Which way are the washrooms?
There.
That's the washroom line.
You have to line up to go
to the washrooms, too?!
It's actually the biggest business here.
Y-You're kidding.
Of course. That's common sense.
Let's go, Minoa.
I'm done.
Let's go back, then.
Uh... Are we lost?
N-Not to worry.
Sebas!
You there! No sliding!
He's not coming.
What do we do, Alice-chan?
もしかしたら迷子になったある?
Could it be that you're lost?
Who is she?
Do you know her, Minoa?
No.
She's pretty, and her outfit's really cute.
Wait, I need to say something.
But what language?
English? French? German?
U-Um...
Spit cakes.
Spit cakes?
Are you hungry?
You can speak Japanese?
Thank goodness.
Yes.
Okay, let's go.
Um...
Wait up!
We're looking for some people.
Am I being abducted?
Hey, Minoacchi, Alicecchi.
Over here.
Senpai!
You took a while.
These two were looking for you.
Oh, they were lost.
Thanks for bringing them back.
Uh, who is she?
She was lined up right behind us.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Could you hold my spot?
Okay, sure.
We talked a bit when I left the line.
Oh, really?
Thank you.
It's okay.
It's important to help each
other out when we're in trouble.
I can't believe you'd get lost when you're
with someone like Alicecchi,
who's been here before—
I'm sorry!
This is actually my first time coming here.
I shouldn't have pretended I knew what I was doing.
Then this wouldn't have happened...
Th-That's not true.
Yes, I think you two would
have gotten lost, either way.
That's harsh.
As a veteran, I should have come with you.
Miko...
Um, this is your first time here?
Just like me.
Really?
Yes!
We were in trouble, but we overcame it.
It wouldn't be good to go home with a
sad experience on our first time here.
You're so...
So let's have fun!
It's a festival, after all!
You're right.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm surprised you remembered
Minoa's face, though.
Not so much her face, but she had that on.
This?
I love Roux:ZERO!
It's huge in Beijing, too.
It's popular in Beijing, too?
Beijing?!
Oh, yeah, she said she's from Beijing.
My name is Yang Beibei.
I'm Asagaya Minoa.
Nihao.
I'm Kamiigusa Alice.
She came here for this event.
That's amazing.
People come from overseas, too?
Well, it's the biggest otaku event in the world!
I've always been dying to come here.
Wait, wasn't Roux:Zero in the spring?
Are there no delays these days?
Almost none.
I've heard that shows used to become popular
six months to a year after disc sales.
It's at the same time nowadays, huh?
It's a problem, sometimes.
It is?
When I tell Japanese people that I like anime,
they deliberately bring up older shows,
even though I want to talk about what's airing.
So their kindness ends up hurting you.
Where do you get information on anime?
Mostly online.
That's just like us.
I see the hype in Japan, and I'm like, "I know, it's so good!"
You can read Japanese?
Well, I guess we're having a
normal conversation right now.
Yes, I'm studying Japanese so I can watch the anime I love.
I met a few people in the US who
could hold simple conversations.
Wow.
Anime's connecting people around the world.
Yup.
The world is connected through anime.
Beibei-san, would you like to join us?
Really?
Yes, I'd love to!
Now we just have to wait for the opening.
It's so hot...
The sun's rising.
It's getting hotter.
And this humidity...
Beibei-chan, are you o—
That's much cooler.
Japanese cooling products are excellent.
You're more prepared than we are.
At least we aren't in direct sunlight.
Look.
K-Kaikai-senpai!
Why is he in the sun?
You won't get me...
You won't get me, damn it!
Line problems.
Okay, it's about to begin.
Beibei,
Don't
Go
It's been half an hour since we were applauding.
It should be about another hour.
An hour?!
We still can't go in!
Just a little longer, Minoa.
Just a little longer.
I'm dying.
The treasure is in sight, everyone.
Pass out now, and you'll
be restarting back at home.
starting back at home.
Huh?
What's going on?
It's an event favorite.
The staff's general warnings.
Be sure to stay hydrated so you don't collapse.
You won't find Akina-sama from Anosuba here.
You won't be getting any water over your heads.
The staff are otaku, too.
It kind of makes the heat more tolerable.
It's time, Minoa.
It was a long time coming.
Yes, but our long journey is finally over.
At last, we're setting foot...
into this new world.
Alice-chan, my heart's pounding.
Mine, too.
But don't be afraid.
Let's open a new door together, Minoa.
Yeah, Alice-chan.
You there, please follow the others inside.
We're finally inside.
Exhausting, huh?
Let's split up, then.
The time has come for me to use
my Unchained Golden Wallet!
All right, here we go.
Just you wait, Shikabari merch!
That way?
I'll use this elite item to hunt you all down!
That way.
There are so many people.
Let's see, where's the Roux:Zero merchandise?
Fliers.
Please take one.
Thank you.
Bags.
So cute.
This is awesome, people are
giving me so much stuff.
Me, too.
Look what I got.
New show starting in fall.
Paper fans.
Take one, please.
These are free.
I-It's so heavy.
They're digging into my shoulders.
Of course it'd be heavy if you took everything.
You could have warned us!
I bought it!
I'm so glad it wasn't sold out.
You worry too much, Minoa.
Oh?
Who was it that was grasping her
wallet with a terrified face?
I'm glad we all got what we wanted.
I know.
Can we get a photo together?
Of course.
Okay.
Come in closer, Minoa.
You too, Miko.
Here we go, guys.
Smile!
Saori-san.
Hey.
Hey, what's up?
Senpai, which college is she from?
Oh, no, she's a cosplay buddy.
She's a fresh young high schooler.
"Fresh young"?
Nice to meet you. I'm Mutsuki.
As you can see, I'm from the
Jouhoku University Anime Club.
I'm Erica.
I'm technically the president of the
anime club at Sakaneko High School.
The anime club at Sakaneko?
Oh, I've heard about it.
It's prestigious, isn't it?
Wait, is it not?
A Sakaneko graduate told me that
their anime club was amazing.
There's just so many people, though.
Obviously.
There are almost 200,000 people here.
Two hundred thousand?!
That many?
Six hundred thousand people in total
over three days, apparently.
You sure know a lot, Beibei-san.
No wonder we have to be in line for hours, with so many people here.
Lining up to get in, lining up once you're in...
It's the harshest event in Japan.
I'm so happy, though.
Happy?
There are so many of my own kind here.
People who love anime and who I can
get excited over the same anime with.
That makes me happy.
Being in line was tough, but I can handle it
since I know I have a lot of friends here.
Plus I got to meet you guys.
Beibei-chan...
Yeah!
I'm glad I got to meet you, too.
Me, too.
Great!
Cool, we're all here.
All right, want to head home?
Shouldn't we wait for Nakano-senpai?
I guess I'll leave him a LINE
message saying we're leaving.
What about you, Beibei-chan?
I want to stay here a little longer.
I'll go wander around a bit more.
Okay.
Minoa, Alice, Miko, Erica, thank you!
Thank you, too.
Bye-bye.
Good day.
I forgot to ask for her contact info.
Oh, yeah.
We screwed up.
And we just became friends.
It's all right.
As long as we're anime lovers,
we'll meet here again.
Yeah.
All right, we should go do
you-know-what on our way home.
Agreed, Erica-senpai.
What's that?
This is so nice.
Lining up sucked, but I bought my
merchandise, and I made a new friend.
Anime events are fun, huh, Alice-chan?
Yes, very.
By the way, what happened
to Musashisakai-senpai?
Huh? Say what?
I can't hear you.
SOLD
OUT
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
That sigh
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Ippo mae ni dete goran
Take a step forward, little lady
Chu!
nikkori tte shite goran
smile big and wide, little lady
Chu!
he no ji no kuchi fukureta kao mo tsuyoi kedo
that frown makes for a nice and tough face,
Chu!
Pokkari to ukanderu
but you're always walking hand-in-hand
Chu!
nakisou na fukidashi wo
with this sad little speech bubble
Chu!
kimi wa itsumo koneko no you ni tsurete iru
like a poor, lost kitten
Chu!
shumi ga koseiteki nandesu
My tastes are peculiar,
chotto
a little
marutto
so I
rikai dekiru yo
understand you completely
dakedo heart wa nozokanai
but I won't peek into your heart
kokoro no door
the door to your feelings
Daisuki na mono oikakete ikitai
I want to chase after what I love
ikou
so let's go
donna ni fukai kemono michi ya mori demo
No matter how many beasts infest the forest
nazo demo
or mysteries
ii nioi suru yokan sakimidareteru
It smells good, and I'm overflowing with anticipation
kyou wa good luck lilac
so good luck, lilac
good luck
lilac
ii koto ga aru
you have good things in your future
Ukiuki wiki hanakotoba wo shirabeta
Guess what? I Wikipedia'd the floriography
Maji ka?
Seriously?
"yuujou hatsukoi seishun no omoide"
and it stands for "friendship, first love, and teenaged memories"
Pride
and "pride"
Dare ni nitenakuttemo kamawanai
I don't care if I'm different from everyone else
moyamoya nara fukitobashichae
I'll just blow the depression away
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
that sigh
hint datta chucchu chu-lilas
was a hint
Don't expect to meet someone
twice on the battlefield.
Next episode: "Someone is Shrouded in Light."
What light? Find out for yourself.