Hello!
Huh?
No one's here?
Damn it, you're so noisy.
You woke me up.
Sorry, I might be here too early,
especially with Alice-chan on cleaning duty.
Hello.
Yes?
Numazon delivery.
Wh-What...
Thank you.
Somebody help!
Ready...
Nani wo shitete mo taikutsu na every day
No matter what I did, I found every day boring
Kokoro odoru you na tokimeki sagashiteta
I searched for something to make my heart dance
Shiranakatta yo kimi ni deau made
Until I met you, I never knew
Mahou mitai ni hirogaru brand new world
of this brand new world that unfolds like magic
Oshiete
So, tell me
Kimi to boku no aikotoba
our secret password
Tsunagaru tsunagaru
It'll connect us
Yuuki wo dashite
so let it be your courage
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can be even stronger
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru yo
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Boku ni wa nai kimi aru mono
As you complement and complete me
Awasareba saikyou ni!
I become the best I can be!
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can shine even brighter
Kira kira ni kagayaku no
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Kimi no "suki" boku no "suki" ga
Mixing your love with my love
Majiwareba saikou ni!
brings out the best in me!
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
Student council room
Anime Club...
I won't give up.
I'll shut down your club.
And...
President.
We've returned. As instructed,
we've researched the club's expenditures,
the members' friendships, their favorite anime...
Everything there is to know about the Anime Club.
I see.
I don't care how insignificant it may seem.
Find any and every issue you can.
Yes.
That was a close one.
You could have helped me,
rather than just saving yourself.
You okay?
Nakano-senpai.
Thank you.
Thank goodness you're okay, my little kitten.
What do you think these boxes are?
Oh.
It looks like they've arrived.
This is all anime?
I ordered it all on Numazon so that we'd
have a collection fit for the Anime Club.
Oh, the special edition Dub Tone movie
Blu-ray with limited-edition packaging.
It has the uncut concert scene too, right?
Oh?
The Chaos Mad Nova box set.
The fan disc has the unthinkable younger sister story too, if I'm not mistaken.
You even got the latest volume of Anosuba.
I can watch the useless goddess Aquina's
barfing scenes over and over in the club room!
We have a nice set of saucers, haven't we?
Saucers?
Not those saucers.
It's what we call physical anime discs.
Disc sales can make or break a late-night anime.
It's a critical matter.
They come with concert raffle tickets
and event invitations and such.
Concerts
Events
Fan-Meets
Concerts
Events
Fan-Meets
Concerts
Events
Fan-Meets
Concerts
Events
Fan-Meets
Concerts
Events
Fan-Meets
Concerts
Events
Fan-Meets
Concerts
Events
Fan-Meets
Concerts
Events
Fan-Meets
The bonus material gets better every year.
They even come with figures or concept art.
Sometimes, you can't even
tell what's the main product.
Fan-Meets
Events
Concerts
People would talk about how the artwork for the TV airing was a disaster,
so the artists would then spend sleepless nights working themselves to death
to upgrade it and turn it into something divine.
Once you reach the master class like I have,
you'll have a copy for storage,
for decorating,
for evangelism,
for watching,
for backup,
along with all the store-specific exclusives.
I don't hesitate to buy multiple copies.
Good for you.
Thus, no matter how much funding I have, it all vanishes into the discs.
The time has come for me to tap
into my Swiss bank account.
Why are they so desperate to sell discs?
Good question.
Airing anime doesn't actually make money.
Making anime costs a lot of money.
So multiple companies invest in a single show,
and create an organization called
a "production committee."
Committee?
Production committees come up with budgets for the anime,
and distribute revenue from the discs and merchandise,
as well as from online streaming
and overseas distribution.
If the sales figures are good,
sometimes they'll even get a second season.
ANIME SEASON 2
ANNOUNCED!!
Sometimes they'd work to hype it up,
and other times they'd change the content of the anime for the sake of business.
They're kind of like a
powerful shadow organization
that has immeasurable influence
over the production.
I never knew.
You see it on the screen in school anime a lot.
For example, in Sakaneko Academy
Private School Student Council.
So then,
the student council is a shadow
organization that controls the school?
Minoa, are you sure you haven't
been watching too much anime?
Although she's probably right in that
you'd be in trouble if you opposed them.
Hey, did you buy all these discs?
Well,
what belongs to the Anime Club belongs to me.
What belongs to me belongs to me.
Wait, so, what?
We've finally got you, Anime Club!
It's them!
The production committee!
Excuse me?
Nothing, we were talking about something else.
So what do you want?
What's got you so eager?
This is your receipt for club spending.
What is "Anime software costs"?
You didn't buy that using club funding, did you?
Don't bother trying to hide it.
The jig is up.
The criminal is among us!
You're correct.
Wait, why are you so quick to confess?
Give me a chance to show off
my Vice President skills!
This is where the treasurer gets to show off.
A total cost of 341,951 yen.
To think you wasted club funding on such a thing.
With all due respect, the club funding belongs to the club members.
That is to say, it belongs to me.
What's wrong with using my own money for myself?
That's what you meant?!
In any case,
a newly-founded Anime Club won't be allowed
to spend such a large amount of money.
Then I'll use my pocket money.
Sebas.
Wait a minute, Alicecchi.
As the president, it's my fault that I
failed to adequately manage the members.
Besides, this is the kind of thing
that we need to solve for ourselves.
Then how about this—
for the next week, you'll assist the
other clubs without compensation.
Unless the student council
approves of the work you do,
the Anime Club will be abolished.
Th-That's too...
Of course you can't.
The Anime Club isn't good for anything.
It can't create anything.
It's just baggage.
There's no way you can do anything
of merit for the other clubs.
You'll have to prove otherwise, if that bothers you.
Prove me wrong.
It'll be interesting.
We just survived getting shut down.
Here you go.
Nakano-senpai.
Thank you.
I never knew we were at the same station.
A heavy-handed student council
threatening to shut down a club.
It's a club anime classic.
I know, right?
I saw something like that on a TV drama.
Yeah, I mean in an anime, though.
Oh. Okay.
So why did you join the Anime Club?
Well...
I think I've always aspired to be
in a club with like-minded people.
The moment we come together and grow as a group
is quite spectacular, don't you think?
Just like that Onotokisaka Academy Idol Club.
Onotokisaka?
It's a legendary high school idol club.
They overcame the student council's sabotaging,
and saved the club from being abolished.
And they were high schoolers?
That's amazing.
We have to do what we can too, then.
Yeah, it was an anime, though.
Let's do this!
We're the Anime Club!
We'd like to support your clubs!
We'll help with anything!
Let us assist you!
Erica-senpai?!
Morning, Minoacchi.
What's up with the outfit?
You could say it's my expression of intent.
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
We will help
your clubs!
Contact us
Club Building 3F
Anime Club
Although it was a bit tight.
I'll help.
Please take a flyer!
We're the Anime Club.
I'll help too!
Alicecchi...
I won't sleep well, seeing the club die.
We have to do what we can.
Handing out fliers is what it's all about.
I'll neither run nor hide.
All pitches, straight down the middle!
That's a game!
Hello, everyone—
I don't understand you.
I feel it...
The dough is cooking inside the electron purgatory.
My magnificent gadget makes
quick work of any confectionery!
Show me, Miko, your most godly move.
It's no use!
We've screwed up at every club we've helped.
Where's Gomon-sensei when you need him?
He's on business abroad this week.
In China, apparently.
He has the worst timing.
We only have two more days.
We're really going to end up being shut down.
This was originally your fault, Alice.
This calls for me to acquire this academy
and take over the student counci-
Your thoughts are possessed by the devil.
It appears so.
Wh-What?!
G-Guys...
That's enough.
This isn't the time to be fighting among ourselves.
Here we go.
It's a request from the Drama Club.
They're performing a musical at school for
the new students the day after tomorrow.
Apparently they didn't get the costumes
they ordered, and they're in a bind.
SAKANEKO
HIGH SCHOOL
DRAMA CLUB
Musical
New Students
Welcome!!
Costumes?
You could make some, couldn't you, Senpai?
I-I guess.
I'll do what I can.
Student council room
That concludes my report.
The Anime Club is making
costumes for the Drama Club?
They're wasting their time.
CLUB
ROOM
GO
BOOM!
Nope.
I can't do it.
Erica-senpai...
The Anime Club isn't good for anything.
It can't create anything.
I'm here from Japan.
My name is Aoyama Erica.
Um...
So...
Hey, wanna come over for Netflix and chill?
H-Hey...
Do you have soft serve?
Yes!
PreFae...
I never knew it was airing here.
Hey, Erica!
This anime's from Japan, right?
You know it?
Yeah, of course.
We're cosplayers, but what do they say
in Japanese when they're transforming?
She's saying...
Enemies of Mother Earth, cease your evil deeds!
Erica-senpai!
Senpai, I have an idea.
Why don't you draw from the
idol anime that I like?
Idol anime?
Yes.
It was in the stack of discs that Alice-chan bought us.
I want to make the world's best costume!
Shall we start with silkworms?
We'll need mulberry fields, too!
Onotoki!
Ono...
...toki!
We did it!
Well?
Don't you think these girls are absolutely dazzling?
Idol anime comes in the
standard school club stories,
Idol Club Philosophy
-
Don't mess up your lines
Don't let them take pictures
-
Don't tell bad jokes
Always smile
14TH NEWCOMER AUDITION
stories about the agency,
regional idols...
all kinds of genres.
The girls depicted in 3D computer
graphics and virtuosic artwork
are absolutely adorable.
Just watching them,
you can almost smell their
sweat and feel their breath.
It's just utterly amazing.
The costumes, too.
Elegant! Fabulous! Excellent!
They accent the girls' beauty beyond words.
I'm going to explode.
Feature these, and I guarantee that
you'll have the best costume ever.
Idol anime always tell the story of an idol group
that begins without cohesion, and comes together.
Go Beauty!
Is that...
That's right.
It's exactly where we are now.
Let's do it, Erica-senpai.
You're still our president, Erica-senpai.
I want to continue this club
with you and everyone else.
Minoacchi...
We do, too.
Guys...
We don't have time.
Nakanocchi and I will design.
Kaikai and Mikocchi, you two find cloth.
Alicecchi and Minoacchi, you two do the tacking.
Start immediately.
Okay!
Wholesale Fabrics Center
It's fine.
I need to make this with my own hands.
Mii-chan, you're still up?
Onee-chan...
I'm almost done.
You're really working hard in the Anime Club, huh?
Hurry, the performance is about to start.
Right!
New Student
Welcome Party
They're never going to get
the costumes done in time.
They may delay the event.
No, I've told the Drama Club that they may
not go over their allotted time in the gym.
Their performance is over, then.
Don't worry.
It's showtime.
Three, two, one.
Impossible.
We barely made it.
We did it!
We can convince the student council now.
No, we don't approve.
You're sorely mistaken if you think you've
done enough to avoid getting shut down.
That silly anime club of yours.
It's not silly.
Anime saved me when I
was alone, studying abroad.
So I'm not going to lose this Anime Club,
this place where we all belong.
It's not true that anime doesn't create anything.
Anime creates a lot of things.
Not just material things,
but interpersonal bonds as well.
Didn't that apply to us too, Tsubaki?
Tsubaki, it's time to transform!
PreFae is two people.
I need one more.
Erica-chan...
Enemies of Mother Earth...
...cease your evil deeds!
You and I aren't the same anymore.
I'm the student president.
I can't let this slide.
Raise the curtains.
Our costumes today were put
together by the Anime Club.
It's thanks to them that our performance was a success.
Please give a grand round of applause.
Thanks for the help!
We got more listeners thanks to you.
We got our club room renovated!
I hate to admit it, but you win this time.
I'll take back abolishing the club.
Tsubaki...
But don't you forget.
I'll never get to like what you like.
Wait, President!
How can you let them off so easily?!
We did it, Erica-senpai.
I'll be more careful about how
I use club funding from now on.
Thanks, guys.
Erica-senpai!
We're dazzling right now.
You're all my beautiful little kittens.
Student council room
Yes.
I failed to shut down the club.
This situation is no longer under my control.
Yes.
Pardon me.
President.
Guess what they did this time!
300,000 yen worth of cosplay costumes!
I don't need any more reports.
It seems your resolve will be further tested, Erica.
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
That sigh
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Ippo mae ni dete goran
Take a step forward, little lady
Chu!
nikkori tte shite goran
smile big and wide, little lady
Chu!
he no ji no kuchi fukureta kao mo tsuyoi kedo
that frown makes for a nice and tough face,
Chu!
Pokkari to ukanderu
but you're always walking hand-in-hand
Chu!
nakisou na fukidashi wo
with this sad little speech bubble
Chu!
kimi wa itsumo koneko no you ni tsurete iru
like a poor, lost kitten
Chu!
shumi ga koseiteki nandesu
My tastes are peculiar,
chotto
a little
marutto
so I
rikai dekiru yo
understand you completely
dakedo heart wa nozokanai
but I won't peek into your heart
kokoro no door
the door to your feelings
Daisuki na mono oikakete ikitai
I want to chase after what I love
ikou
so let's go
donna ni fukai kemono michi ya mori demo
No matter how many beasts infest the forest
nazo demo
or mysteries
ii nioi suru yokan sakimidareteru
It smells good, and I'm overflowing with anticipation
kyou wa good luck lilac
so good luck, lilac
good luck
lilac
ii koto ga aru
you have good things in your future
Ukiuki wiki hanakotoba wo shirabeta
Guess what? I Wikipedia'd the floriography
Maji ka?
Seriously?
"yuujou hatsukoi seishun no omoide"
and it stands for "friendship, first love, and teenaged memories"
Pride
and "pride"
Dare ni nitenakuttemo kamawanai
I don't care if I'm different from everyone else
moyamoya nara fukitobashichae
I'll just blow the depression away
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
that sigh
hint datta chucchu chu-lilas
was a hint
Anime, back in the day, had people
become idols with just a bit of magic.
It was totally filled with dreams!
Idol anime these days have them
legit practicing and auditioning.
Tough times we live in.
Next episode: "The Anime Club
Gets a Spot Along the Wall!"
Don't stay up all night.