Morning.
My, you're up early.
I couldn't stay asleep.
Honey...
Take a look at this.
Oh, this is from when we got married.
It came out when I was
cleaning out the drawers.
I look so young.
I was pretty cute, don't you think?
You're still cute, honey.
Oh, stop.
It's like I'm in a dream,
being married to you, Ai-chan.
Oh, Shugo-kun.
Ai-chan.
Shugo-kun.
Ai-chan!
Shugo-kun!
Oh, crap!
Hey, Onee-chan, did you...
Not right now.
I'm running late.
Ouch.
Huh?
You quit your club, didn't you?
It was the yearbook committee
meeting this morning.
See ya.
Onee-chan!
What's wrong, Minoa?
D-Did you just see her face...
Hey!
Jeez.
Yuicching!
Nani wo shitete mo taikutsu na every day
No matter what I did, I found every day boring
Kokoro odoru you na tokimeki sagashiteta
I searched for something to make my heart dance
Shiranakatta yo kimi ni deau made
Until I met you, I never knew
Mahou mitai ni hirogaru brand new world
of this brand new world that unfolds like magic
Oshiete
So, tell me
Kimi to boku no aikotoba
our secret password
Tsunagaru tsunagaru
It'll connect us
Yuuki wo dashite
so let it be your courage
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can be even stronger
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru yo
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Boku ni wa nai kimi aru mono
As you complement and complete me
Awasareba saikyou ni!
I become the best I can be!
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can shine even brighter
Kira kira ni kagayaku no
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Kimi no "suki" boku no "suki" ga
Mixing your love with my love
Majiwareba saikou ni!
brings out the best in me!
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
Their faces changed?
Yeah, although it didn't last for long.
They changed? How?
How?
Oh, they looked really flat,
like in an old anime.
You must be tired, Minoa.
A lot has happened since the school festival.
Please believe me!
I swear...
Morning.
Y-Yui-chan!
Don't they look weird?
Weird?
Their faces!
How rude!
What about them?
What?!
Can't you tell?
Huh?
First class is art.
We need to switch classrooms.
Come on, let's go.
Okay.
What?
What the hell?
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Did you just see that?
That black thing.
The dark abyss, engulfing all creation.
Hell, hell, hell, or something!
Get a grip, Minoa.
There's nothing there.
There was!
You walk up to about here, and...
Did you eat something weird?
Minoa's seeing things that we can't see.
Shall we go to the nurse's office?
No, I swear I saw it.
Wait...
I'm so hungry.
Minoa, what are you doing for lunch?
Packed lunch?
Want to go buy bread?
Lunch B is chicken katsu.
That sounds good, too.
Minoa, we're having a club meeting during lunch.
That was definitely weird.
Class just ended instantly.
No way.
It's only been a little more than
a minute since the first class.
Calm your nerves with some of this.
Sebas.
A maid?
Bring me the usual.
Understood.
Leave it to me.
She spoke!
S'il vous plaît.
Excelsior, Sebas.
Splendid footwork, Sebas-chan.
Would you like to join the track club?
Here.
Lucky.
Can I have some?
Sure.
Thank you.
Ooh, me too!
Sparkly eyes!
What did you take?
Minoa, you're right.
Something's wrong.
You finally get it?
Sebas serves Earl Grey at this time of the day.
This is Houjicha.
That?
That's what's wrong?
|
| |
Anime Club
About the club president for next year...
This is wrong!
How is it wrong?
Every club is talking about
the transition right now.
I'm not talking about that.
I mean, everything's gone sideways.
Everything has?
Minoa's been like this all day.
Weird?
What would you class as weird?
That thing right there, for starters!
Are you seeing something, Minoa-chan?
You must have acquired the
power of the evil eye.
I have not!
Haven't you noticed everything's changed?
Has it?
I suppose it has.
Well, now that you mention it...
The series composition might have changed.
The series composition?
No way.
Now, of all times?
Did Tahiro run away?
Would it even matter if he actually left?
Huh? What?
What are you talking about?
This calls for confirmation.
Want to watch the opening again, then?
Agreed.
Opening?
Again?
I'm going to rewind.
Opening?
Want to watch the opening again, then?
This calls for confirmation.
Huh? What?
Would it even matter if he actually left?
Did Tahiro run away?
Now, of all times?
The series composition?
The series composition might have changed.
Well, now that you mention it...
I suppose it has.
Has it?
Haven't you noticed everything's changed?
I have not!
Are you seeing something, Minoa-chan?
That thing right there, for starters!
What would you class as weird?
Minoa's been like this all day.
I mean, everything's gone sideways.
I'm not talking about that.
Every club is talking about
the transition right now.
This is wrong!
That's what's wrong?
This is Houjicha.
Sebas serves Earl Grey at this time of the day.
You finally get it?
Something's wrong.
Minoa, you're right.
Sparkly eyes!
Thank you.
Can I have some?
Would you like to join the track club?
Splendid footwork, Sebas-chan.
S'il vous plaît.
Leave it to me.
Sebas.
Calm your nerves with some of this.
It's only been a little more than
a minute since the first class.
Minoa, we're having a club meeting during lunch.
Lunch B is chicken katsu.
Packed lunch?
Wait...
Shall we go to the nurse's office?
Minoa's seeing things that we can't see.
There was!
There's nothing there.
Hell, hell, hell, or something!
That black thing.
Did you just see that?
What?
We need to switch classrooms.
Can't you tell?
Weird?
Please believe me!
A lot has happened since the school festival.
Oh, they looked really flat,
like in an old anime.
How?
Yeah, although it didn't last for long.
Their faces changed?
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
Majiwareba saikou ni!
brings out the best in me!
Kimi no "suki" boku no "suki" ga
Mixing your love with my love
Kira kira ni kagayaku no
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can shine even brighter
Awasareba saikyou ni!
I become the best I can be!
Boku ni wa nai kimi aru mono
As you complement and complete me
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru yo
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can be even stronger
Yuuki wo dashite
so let it be your courage
Tsunagaru tsunagaru
It'll connect us
Kimi to boku no aikotoba
our secret password
Oshiete
So, tell me
Mahou mitai ni hirogaru brand new world
of this brand new world that unfolds like magic
Shiranakatta yo kimi ni deau made
Until I met you, I never knew
Kokoro odoru you na tokimeki sagashiteta
I searched for something to make my heart dance
Nani wo shitete mo taikutsu na every day
No matter what I did, I found every day boring
Yuicching!
Jeez.
Nani wo shitete mo taikutsu na every day
No matter what I did, I found every day boring
SERIES COMPOSITION     HIROTA MITSUTAKA
It's still him.
Wait, what's going on?
Why are you all okay with this?
Calm down, Minoa.
Jump the shark too much now,
and they'll cancel us at episode 11.
Cancel us at episode 11?
Because it's too different from
what's been happening so far?
They'll accuse us of not sticking to a genre.
What genre will make them happy?
Slice-of-life?
School?
Moe?
Otome?
Genre classifications are becoming
more and more complicated by the year.
We may need to at least settle on whether
it's a gag show or a realistic show.
Then it's time to explode.
Explode?
Anti-flash, anti-blast.
See, now it's comedy.
My eyes... My eyes!
And this is if we're realistic.
Yet we're alive.
It's not fully realistic.
What would happen if it were?
Let's do it.
You better buy me mackerel sashimi.
Neko-senpai!
It's realistic.
It's definitely realistic.
Realism...
...is amazing.
Neko-senpai!
Our Friend Kouki's
Second Betrayal
Are you all right?
I thought I was dead.
Minoa-chan, are you not going home yet?
I wanted to talk to Neko-senpai some more.
All right.
You've been overreacting today,
so I was a bit worried.
Sorry.
Everyone's totally decided that I'm the weird one.
See you.
Aurora-senpai.
Aurora-senpai?
Nakano-senpai?
Yes?
U-Um...
You said you had five siblings, right?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
Is your oldest brother a lot older than you?
Say, by 20 years.
Not even close.
Why?
Oh, never mind, then.
Sorry.
See you.
What's this about his siblings?
Oh, it's nothing.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
It looked like it was raining earlier.
Were you okay?
You're home late.
Sorry, we already watched the
recording of Tennen Maid.
Mii-chan?
I-I'm home.
Thank goodness.
What's wrong?
You're such a silly girl.
Sorry, we already watched Molly the Witch, too.
Oh my God!
Shall we start dinner?
I'll help.
Me too, then.
Thank you.
Let's race to the kitchen, then!
Hoy, sir!
It looks delicious.
Here.
Thanks.
The Next Day
Ow!
This is bad!
What's wrong?
A Gigamachinju showed up in the city.
A Gigamachinju?
It's headed our way.
Settle down!
We're safe.
I've already set up a barrier.
Well, at least Kaikai-senpai doesn't
seem any different from usual.
Musashisakai Kai!
RIGHT
LEFT
Guren Shoot!
That's a bit too much firepower.
How?
How can you all be so okay with this?
This is wrong!
It's not like we're in an anime!
"It's not like we're in an anime"?
This is great.
Is there a problem?
You've been talking crazy since yesterday.
What has your soul been possessed by?
Get a grip, I'm begging you!
Anime is anime.
It's not reality.
You're the ones acting crazy.
Are you rejecting anime?
What a terrifying child!
I thought you loved the
Anime Club more than anyone.
And yet...
Wait a second.
What a terrifying child!
Alice-chan!
Is it truly a love of anime if one
doesn't accept every aspect of anime?
I'm done with you.
I'm disappointed.
Why?
Why is it suddenly sunset?!
I'm done with you.
Are you rejecting anime?
Autumn Wars
Replica
What?
No...
No.
No!
Mii-chan, what's wrong?
Am I weird?
Am I not normal?
Is there something wrong with me?
Mii-chan...
Of course there isn't.
Hang on just a little longer.
We're almost at the ending.
The Next Day
Morning.
Good morning.
Morning!
Morning.
Weird, I feel like everyone's staring at me.
What do you expect?
I heard you said you hate anime.
I never...
said that!
Good day.
Morning.
Aurora-senpai.
Could you please not call me by that name?
You're right that something's changed.
Senpai...
I might not have noticed
if you hadn't mentioned it.
Thank goodness.
I thought I was the one going crazy.
There must be a cause.
A cause?
A cause for all the unusual
things that are happening.
Can you think of anything?
Unusual things?
It's all your doing, isn't it?
Huh?
I knew it was weird that you could talk!
You're pointing that out now?
When I first opened the door, there you were.
Indeed, thank you.
And you told me not to open the door again.
Everything's gotten weirder and weirder
since Nakano-senpai and the
others started talking to you.
You must be the cause of all of this!
Is that right?
Now, let's get to the bottom of this.
W-Wait!
The door...
And now it's my turn!
Behold! Black Red Blue Yellow Golden Dragon!
Summon!
Alice-chan! Miko-chan!
What?
Even I've become an anime...?
The shackles have been broken.
Senpai?
With the Observer absent,
order will be destroyed.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?!
Are you from the other side?
That's right.
The anime side.
Just like you.
You're from an anime, Neko-senpai?
That's what you choose to react to?!
This world will soon be engulfed in anime.
Engulfed?
Who do you work for?
He has arrived.
New World Big Bang!
Guys...
This is reality.
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
That sigh
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Ippo mae ni dete goran
Take a step forward, little lady
Chu!
nikkori tte shite goran
smile big and wide, little lady
Chu!
he no ji no kuchi fukureta kao mo tsuyoi kedo
that frown makes for a nice and tough face,
Chu!
Pokkari to ukanderu
but you're always walking hand-in-hand
Chu!
nakisou na fukidashi wo
with this sad little speech bubble
Chu!
kimi wa itsumo koneko no you ni tsurete iru
like a poor, lost kitten
Chu!
shumi ga koseiteki nandesu
My tastes are peculiar,
chotto
a little
marutto
so I
rikai dekiru yo
understand you completely
dakedo heart wa nozokanai
but I won't peek into your heart
kokoro no door
the door to your feelings
Daisuki na mono oikakete ikitai
I want to chase after what I love
ikou
so let's go
donna ni fukai kemono michi ya mori demo
No matter how many beasts infest the forest
nazo demo
or mysteries
ii nioi suru yokan sakimidareteru
It smells good, and I'm overflowing with anticipation
kyou wa good luck lilac
so good luck, lilac
good luck
lilac
ii koto ga aru
you have good things in your future
Ukiuki wiki hanakotoba wo shirabeta
Guess what? I Wikipedia'd the floriography
Maji ka?
Seriously?
"yuujou hatsukoi seishun no omoide"
and it stands for "friendship, first love, and teenaged memories"
Pride
and "pride"
Dare ni nitenakuttemo kamawanai
I don't care if I'm different from everyone else
moyamoya nara fukitobashichae
I'll just blow the depression away
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
that sigh
hint datta chucchu chu-lilas
was a hint
Did we even talk about anime today?
The title Anime-Gataris means
"Anime Talk," doesn't it?
Wait, let's check the opening again.
Yuicching!
Yuicching...
Yuicching?!
What a terrifying girl.
What was once old is new again!
And next, here comes the title card.
"Anime-Non-Talk"?!