All right, here's to a successful
school festival concert.
|
| |
Anime Club
Cheers!
Thank you for a successful
school festival after-party!
Great job, everyone!
Yeah, great job.
Great job!
You hold after-parties when
you finish an anime too, huh?
They're held at rather lavish venues.
Or so I've heard.
It's like a festival at the
end of the project, after all.
I've heard they have bingo parties and stuff.
They're supposed to be gorgeous.
FIGHT! ONOTOKISAKA ACADEMY
IDOL CLUB!
Good work!
I've seen them on social media,
having cake with the characters printed on it.
It's also a time for those who have little interaction with each other to come together.
That sounds fun.
I heard they have trouble
deciding what to wear, though.
And that arranging for the parties is hard.
It's hard to work around the staff and cast's schedule.
The popular ones must be really busy.
I've heard that the writers
feel completely out of place.
Completely out of place?
A lot of time passes between when the
script is written and the after-party.
They're in a totally different frame of mind compared to the rest of the staff
who'd just finished making the anime, huh?
No one needs the screenwriters.
That's not true, I'm sure.
The school president council hasn't said anything, huh?
I heard she got sick after the school festival.
She hasn't come to school, either.
I guess I was hoping for too much,
thinking we could patch things up
while emotions were running high.
That anime short had me seriously pumped.
I was hoping we could get it completely finished.
The event was a blast.
Let's just call it a win.
It was worth the effort.
Worth the effort, huh?
Yui-chan?
I was just thinking how life doesn't
really work out like in anime.
Did something happen?
I can't jump the way I want to these days.
Oh, your high jumps.
I can't break my record.
I'm doing the best I can, but...
Yeah?
At times like these, Musashisakai-senpai
would be like, "Look at the saddle!"
That's an anime classic.
Saddle?
It's from a club about a bike racing
anime called Nakimushi Saddle.
Watching them, your hands get
all sweaty as you cheer them on.
It's not about track club, but I
think it could give you inspiration.
Maybe I should give it a watch.
If you like...
I'll lend you my blu-rays.
Really?
Thanks!
Yui-chan, you watch anime?
Yeah, I've started getting into it.
I think you've influenced me.
It's fun once you start watching.
Right?
Hina, Hina, Hina...
Yui-chan!
Hina! Hina!
Morning, Minoa.
M-Morning.
That song you were just singing...
It's the Hina song from Saddle.
The one Azemichi-kun sang.
Hi!
Breathe to the rhythm of the shouts, and bam!
Thanks for the awesome song, Obata.
This is thanks to the Anime Club, too.
Hina! Hina! Hina!
Thanks.
Y-You're welcome.
Okay, see you in class.
As long as they're finding it useful, I guess.
|
| |
Anime Club
A baseball anime?
We want advice...
...like you gave the track club.
Please!
Um...
You've come to the right place.
Passion!
Hard work!
Victory!
These are the things that sports
anime are perfect at expressing.
And thus sports themes are a staple in anime.
There are a ton of baseball classics,
including Miracle Titans Mudou-kun
and Ace of the Bench.
Being able to show off a lot of characters
is one of the nice things about sports anime.
You can have a perfect assortment
of unique, attractive characters.
It's nice that everyone's
in matching uniforms, too.
There's a sense of camaraderie.
Cosplaying them with your friends is great, too.
Even the often-mocked, hyperbolic training
scenes and impossible techniques
are perfectly fine handled in the style
of a special ability battle anime.
Take this!
Lightning mach ba—
Morning, Minoacchi.
Um, Erica-senpai...
I'm not giving up!
Huh...
It's Mudou-kun's Lighting Mach Ball.
Shouldn't we stop him?
He's going to hurt himself.
Mornin'!
I'm starting my trick throw training!
That's great.
I'm glad we helped you out.
Next club, please.
Alice-chan, what is this?
Isn't it amazing?
Everyone's asking for advice.
A grudge practice match?
You need to watch the Fresh Prince
of Tennis: Kanto Regionals, then.
Build your empire on a cool, collected mind.
I get it.
You can't win in the robot competition?
That's why you're a fool!
Tengen Bakuha Guden Daran!
Best everything with your drill!
Bro!
You haven't won a single match yet?
Then Slash Dunk and
Tarako's Basketball are for you.
The game ends when you give up.
We want to play basketball, Anime Club.
Thank you!
Giving advice...
When did you kids become so influential?
Neko-senpai...
Behold... The Frozen World!
I'll destroy you, basketball and all!
Hammer of Destruction!
|
| |
Anime Club
If you want to be better at mahjong,
you need to watch Shake.
Mahjong is such fun.
You want to win the competition?
You need Timbre! French Horn.
If you stand on a bridge and shout
"I want to get better!" it'll be perfect.
I hate it when it's noisy.
Hey, it's a cat.
Nyan-nyanko-sensei!
He looks just like Yabanyan.
So cute!
Aww.
Q-Quit it.
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye-nyan!
Well, there's nothing wrong
with helping people in need.
Right.
I don't think there's anything wrong with it.
It's helping people, and no one's getting hurt.
True.
I know, but...
Wait, you know what Neko-senpai
is saying, Nakano-senpai?
Yeah.
By the way, speaking of sports anime...
Repeating pans!
Three times, at that!
And sketch filters.
Don't forget the God Rays, too.
I have no idea what you two are talking about.
Minoa!
Yui-chan.
I heard the Anime Club's huge right now.
That's amazing!
Oh, these?
The robotics club helped me out.
They're amazing. They speed up
like crazy when you run!
Apparently they took inspiration
from anime for these, too.
But isn't that cheating?
I think I can break my record now!
Okay, I'm getting back to practice.
Dash mode.
Vwoom!
Yui-chan!
Are you all right?!
I'm fine.
Ow...
Obata, that's enough!
The
Anime
Club:
Forever
Snobs
Vwoom!
Nani wo shitete mo taikutsu na every day
No matter what I did, I found every day boring
Kokoro odoru you na tokimeki sagashiteta
I searched for something to make my heart dance
Shiranakatta yo kimi ni deau made
Until I met you, I never knew
Mahou mitai ni hirogaru brand new world
of this brand new world that unfolds like magic
Oshiete
So, tell me
Kimi to boku no aikotoba
our secret password
Tsunagaru tsunagaru
It'll connect us
Yuuki wo dashite
so let it be your courage
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can be even stronger
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru yo
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Boku ni wa nai kimi aru mono
As you complement and complete me
Awasareba saikyou ni!
I become the best I can be!
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can shine even brighter
Kira kira ni kagayaku no
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Kimi no "suki" boku no "suki" ga
Mixing your love with my love
Majiwareba saikou ni!
brings out the best in me!
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
Are you pumped for this week's Show Up Rockin'?
Sure.
Whaaat?!
You shouldn't neglect Dad.
Hey, what kind of practice does your club do?
The lacrosse club?
Nothing special.
We practice sprinting and
swinging the crosse and stuff.
Would you ever, say, mod your stick
so you could shoot really far?
No way, that would be cheating.
That would be an anime, Minoa.
I know, right?
The martial arts club's training grounds.
It's coming along nicely.
The martial arts club's training grounds?
I heard they're going to duel
at the top of that pyramid.
Isn't that dangerous?
Look, Minoa, there's the Go Volleyball Club.
Go Volleyball Club?!
All right, begin!
The hand of God!
It looks like the Anime Club's advice is really paying off.
Yup.
The whole school is brimming with life.
There you all are.
The robotics club is about do
a test launch on its prototype.
It's finally complete?!
Let's go watch it, Minoa.
Wait, test launch?
All right.
King Sakaneko Legs-only Version, commence!
Sakaneko Academy's scientific prowess is unrivaled!
This doesn't look good...
Thank you.
Something's wrong.
Prototypes are supposed to be more
capable than the mass-production units.
It's a prototype. What can you do?
|
| |
Anime Club
When do you think that robot will be finished, Minoa?
I've got big news!
What is it, Sensei?
We're getting a TV interview!
TV?
TV? You mean...
The thing that sends us anime?!
Although it's just a local cable TV station.
They want to report on this unique school
that incorporates anime into its training.
That's splendid, Sensei.
This is amazing, Minoa!
Y-Yeah.
At last!
At last, our time has come!
We can finally win!
It's my TV debut.
This beautiful, young light novel
author might get a book deal.
How should I dress?
Should I cosplay?
Barbers!
I need to go to the barber shop!
But I shall have to conceal the power
of my evil eye in front of the camera.
Autographs!
I need to think of an autograph!
|
| |
Anime Club
I'll be heading home.
Alice-chan and the others seem really happy.
And the people in the other clubs are working hard.
But...
Is it all so weird that you feel
like you're the only sane one?
Yeah.
But you aren't alone.
You've always had someone by your side.
Alice-chan!
Alice-chan?!
Forget it!
Go have that dude cheer you up.
Who?
You left by yourself, so I got a bit worried.
Minoa-chan, you gained something by joining this club, didn't you?
Something I gained?
Alice-chan, Miko-chan, the senpais...
Everyone loves anime, and I have
friends that I can talk about it to.
I have lots of happy memories.
That's right.
Anime has the power to connect
people and make them happy.
That's exactly what's happening now.
Anime connected us to the people
in the other clubs, too.
And anime's making everyone happy.
It's a happy ending.
What you and the Anime Club
did together wasn't a mistake.
That's why we're getting an interview.
Yeah.
Maybe you're right.
The Anime Club proposes incorporating anime-style approaches to training in all clubs.
It was my idea!
Anime-inspired training appears absurd at first,
but in order to break through your
shell and exceed your limits,
you need a certain degree of daring.
That has always been my conviction.
Free ideas, unrestrained by common sense.
That's the greatest allure and strength of anime.
Humanity knows no limits.
The strength to believe we can go anywhere.
That's the power of anime.
That is what I have taught them every day.
I did! It was all me!
It's a new record.
Yay!
Congratulations, Yui-chan.
Thanks.
This is all thanks to the anime that
you and your friends told me about.
What you did wasn't a mistake.
Wasn't a mistake...
Thank goodness for anime.
This isn't much, but...
Sakana Cable TV, Co.
Thank you
No, I'd rather not.
It's fine, Sensei.
Let's just add it to our club funding.
But...
We can buy another VHD deck.
Sakana Cable TV, Co.
Thank you
Why, thank you.
Sakana Cable TV, Co.
Thank you
All right.
Let's call it a day.
Okay.
What shall I watch when I get home?
I think I'll watch Dirlish Bumper.
I like the protagonist's wacky personality.
Her catch phrase...
We win.
It's from Tsubaki.
That's the one.
Be careful
"Be careful"?
Of what?
hurry up and get bet
Be careful
hurry up and get bett
hurry up and get bette
hurry up and get better
I don't know what
you're talking about,
but hurry up and
get better
The Anime Club is hereby...
...being shut down.
Ignored?!
Sure.
The club's about to get shut down.
How many times has this happened now?
What is this, recycled content?
You won't be so indifferent for long!
Why, you ask?
Because it was this man...
...who declared it so!
Pri—
Principal!
Principal?
Is he really?
This is my first time seeing him.
What?!
You people have seen him at
the school gate every day!
The school gate?
The artwork's starting to suck!
Guys...
To think I would step foot in here once again.
Again?
It's an order straight from the principal this time.
No grace period.
One strike and you're out!
Th-This is tyranny!
You don't even have a reason to shut us down.
Sakaneko Academy Code Article 13 Section 2:
"A club shall not receive money for its
activities outside of the academy's allocations."
Receiving money?!
Wh-When did you guys do that?!
We didn't!
Come on.
Sensei, you totally took money.
President, he did indeed take
Sakana Cable TV, Co.
Thank you
gratuities from the TV crew.
Sakana Cable TV, Co.
Thank you
N-Nakano...
Oh, you already bought the deck.
Sensei!
Please don't use club funds
without saying anything!
Look who's talking.
The Anime Club is to be shut down.
Gomon-sensei is suspended from duty.
No!
Good work, Nakano-kun.
Nakano-senpai!
Why?
Aurora!
You screwed us over, Aurora!
Please don't call me that.
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
That sigh
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Ippo mae ni dete goran
Take a step forward, little lady
Chu!
nikkori tte shite goran
smile big and wide, little lady
Chu!
he no ji no kuchi fukureta kao mo tsuyoi kedo
that frown makes for a nice and tough face,
Chu!
Pokkari to ukanderu
but you're always walking hand-in-hand
Chu!
nakisou na fukidashi wo
with this sad little speech bubble
Chu!
kimi wa itsumo koneko no you ni tsurete iru
like a poor, lost kitten
Chu!
shumi ga koseiteki nandesu
My tastes are peculiar,
chotto
a little
marutto
so I
rikai dekiru yo
understand you completely
dakedo heart wa nozokanai
but I won't peek into your heart
kokoro no door
the door to your feelings
Daisuki na mono oikakete ikitai
I want to chase after what I love
ikou
so let's go
donna ni fukai kemono michi ya mori demo
No matter how many beasts infest the forest
nazo demo
or mysteries
ii nioi suru yokan sakimidareteru
It smells good, and I'm overflowing with anticipation
kyou wa good luck lilac
so good luck, lilac
good luck
lilac
ii koto ga aru
you have good things in your future
Ukiuki wiki hanakotoba wo shirabeta
Guess what? I Wikipedia'd the floriography
Maji ka?
Seriously?
"yuujou hatsukoi seishun no omoide"
and it stands for "friendship, first love, and teenaged memories"
Pride
and "pride"
Dare ni nitenakuttemo kamawanai
I don't care if I'm different from everyone else
moyamoya nara fukitobashichae
I'll just blow the depression away
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
that sigh
hint datta chucchu chu-lilas
was a hint
Never forgive a traitor.
That is the code of the Cat Knighthood.
Next episode, someone changes their ways?
Whose name does the traitor know?
Watch Again
Gataris