The Anime Club is to be shut down.
Nakano-senpai, why?
You screwed us over, Aurora!
Please don't call me that.
Nani wo shitete mo taikutsu na every day
No matter what I did, I found every day boring
Kokoro odoru you na tokimeki sagashiteta
I searched for something to make my heart dance
Shiranakatta yo kimi ni deau made
Until I met you, I never knew
Mahou mitai ni hirogaru brand new world
of this brand new world that unfolds like magic
Oshiete
So, tell me
Kimi to boku no aikotoba
our secret password
Tsunagaru tsunagaru
It'll connect us
Yuuki wo dashite
so let it be your courage
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can be even stronger
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru yo
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Boku ni wa nai kimi aru mono
As you complement and complete me
Awasareba saikyou ni!
I become the best I can be!
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can shine even brighter
Kira kira ni kagayaku no
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Kimi no "suki" boku no "suki" ga
Mixing your love with my love
Majiwareba saikou ni!
brings out the best in me!
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
I gave the club room keys
back to the student council.
I see.
Sorry, this is my fault.
This wouldn't have happened
if I'd been more careful.
No.
It's not your fault, Erica-senpai.
Damn it, Aurora!
I can't believe I didn't notice his evil conspiracy.
I should have known.
The Anime Club's gone, huh?
The school festival was such a blast, too.
Yeah.
Even if we lost this house,
we would still be family.
What are you talking about?
Darling, don't tell me you
might get laid off again?!
Again?!
I was speaking hypothetically!
Wait, so what're you getting at?
Even without the container that is
the house, a family is a family.
Friends are still friends.
Hurry!
Yeah!
What?
NO SHUTTING DOWN
ANIME CLUB
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
NO SHUTTING DOWN
ANIME CLUB
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
Get out here, Principal!
NO SHUTTING DOWN
ANIME CLUB
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
Don't disband the Anime Club!
What's going on?
Minoa.
Over here.
What on Earth is going on?
I have no idea.
We can't live without the Anime Club!
To think people need us this much...
This is a bit extreme, though.
Listen up, students.
It's the principal.
NO SHUTTING DOWN
ANIME CLUB
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
If you want the Anime Club's
shutdown to be withdrawn,
then this school is hereby closed.
NO SHUTTING DOWN
ANIME CLUB
Don't allow
the principal's
tyranny!!
Is this what you want?
Yes.
All it takes to silence small fry
is to take them out of the water.
Principal's Office
Come out, Ogikubo!
Explain this!
Principal's Office
I can't.
I've been ordered not to let anyone through.
No, don't touch me!
If you really want to get in,
you'll have to defeat me first.
You'll have to push me down by force!
People are enraged.
I'm kind of scared.
Move it!
That's too rough!
Oh, crap!
What the...
You idiot, you just made it lock.
You're all coming with me to the staff office.
This is one of my feeding spots.
What are you doing, Senpai?
Don't just stand there—help me.
Ow...
Principal?
P-Pardon me.
I'm Asagaya Minoa, first-year
student from the Anime Club.
I heard Minoa's voice.
Minoa, open up!
They might not be able to hear us from inside.
Why do you hate the Anime Club so much?
What the hell was that?
The anime short for the school festival.
You broke the 180-degree rule.
The artwork broke down.
The lines were read monotonously.
It was a barrage of amateurish jokes.
How dare you!
I poured my soul into that work of art!
I hate to admit it, but he has a point.
I actually thought so, too.
Worse, you held a concert because
you couldn't finish the ending.
The title is too long!
U-Uh...
Do you have anything to say for yourself?
You actually paid that much attention to it?!
Thank you so much!
What a passionate roast.
The title is too long...
Is the principal an anime fan?
Then why is he trying to take the
Anime Club down the path of destruction?
Parts of it may have been bad,
but it's the best piece ever,
filled with my favorite anime.
Your favorite anime?
It's the anime that I saw when I was a kid.
Robots going bam!
Grandpas going boom!
A girl's song defeats the enemy,
a fish goes flippy flippy flappy,
and an angel descends.
I still have dreams about it.
Burndown, Stretch Dawn,
Mermaid Melody Pichipichipacchi,
and Andromeda Angel.
All masterpieces.
So how did they end up the way they did?
Wow, you know so much about anime!
But those aren't the anime I love.
What was it called?
I don't remember.
You say that with such confidence!
You're in the Anime Club,
and you can't even remember titles?
Is the girl from Strange Midia?
The giant mech, is it GahXephon?
Defeating an enemy with singing,
is that Super Dimension Bonsai Micross?
Is the angel from A Dog of Decadence?
Those aren't it.
The principal sure likes picking
fights with the Anime Club.
He's acting like a club senior.
Come to think of it, the rough sketches in
the club room were like Midia and GahXephon.
Maybe the principal was in the Anime Club.
Let's find out.
A cute anime girl.
The raw depiction of a girl in the scene
where Mei Minling is given a choice
between her life and her hair,
and she chooses her hair, was shocking.
Bishoujo Fighter Sailor Bunny was the
first shoujo battle heroine manga.
There would never be enough time to
talk about the heart-filled final episode.
And man, Ham-chan in
Nurusei Yakara is so devoted.
I want to cheat on her so she'll zap me.
Hiatari Sokosoko! and Kimamani Mikan Road are the two best slice-of-life bishoujo anime.
Ayuyama was based on an idol that
was really popular at the time.
Holy crap, that's him!
From anime fan to anti-anime.
What happened to him?
Maybe he was an aspiring
writer who came to hate anime
after he was asked to rewrite the school
festival script, like, 58 times.
We're protecting the school
and the Anime Club ourselves!
What pests.
Back before the Internet,
we read Animeta with hunger.
I'm getting all of this down!
It's too late.
Your school festival anime will
haunt you for the rest of your life.
Hey, now!
Making anime is hard, you know.
A battle of passion and personality.
Looming deadlines and dwindling stamina...
But it is the work of the director to bring
the minds and talent together as one.
You don't get to talk like you're a director!
A director is a much more high-minded,
noble, solitary figure.
He stands alone!
Nothing gets done without the director!
Worship the director more!
Suck up to them!
I understand.
I totally understand.
She totally doesn't.
What a stuffy conversation, though.
Do you think the principal might have been an anime director?
It's possible.
Aurora!
Why are you here?
I'm sorry!
I have my reasons for doing this.
We don't need your excuses, Aurora-senpai.
It's too late, Aurora-senpai.
You see, I have five siblings.
Six Aurora-senpais?!
My older brothers are all complete losers, and—
On second thought, let's not go there.
Anyway, I worked my butt off
at a high-class coffee shop.
The principal was a regular there.
With my family's financial problems,
I wasn't sure I should attend high school.
That's when he gave me a hand.
That's why I can't go against what he says.
It was so terrible.
Aurora-senpai, I had no idea.
Yet you were always smiling.
Aurora, damn it, man!
Bliss!
I can't blame you, then.
Welcome back, Auroracchi.
Thanks, everyone.
Also, can you stop calling me Aurora?
The director is number one!
Of course!
After talking to you, I'm as pumped
as ever to get back to work.
Back to work?
I'll work even harder on the second piece.
Second piece?
Because I love anime.
Even without the Anime Club, we're friends.
As long as we're together,
we can make a second one.
There will be no second one.
Everything's over if you
screw up the first episode.
Even if you devote your entire
being into creating two seasons,
if the first episode gets canceled, it's all over!
What's going on?
It's not my fault!
It's the anime fans' fault!
Every damn night, they gather in the corners of the Internet, whining and complaining.
Who the hell is "anon" anyway? Screw you all!
Have you made anime before, Principal?
So he was a director.
But it got canned after the first episode?
He got dissed too hard—it broke him.
As a fellow creator, I have nothing but sympathy.
My work was banished into oblivion!
What a pain.
Neko-chan.
It's Neko-senpai!
That's cold!
There's a cat door here.
He's surprisingly fond of cats.
Minoa, are you all right?
Alice-chan?
Open up.
Uh...
There are a ton of buttons... I don't know...
Principal, what's the password?
He can't hear your voices right now.
The lock to the door is the
lock to his heart, perhaps.
Lock to his heart?
He probably means that until the principal
opens his heart, it will never open.
What are you, chuuni?
You're one to talk.
A password that would open his heart?
If he broke down because of anime,
he can only be saved through anime.
Indeed.
A ray of light at the end of the darkness.
Let's find it!
Yeah.
Begin M-Project.
Ambitious start!
Minoa, I promise I'll find the principal's anime.
And I'll save you.
A-As soon as possible, please.
Anime
Club
Finally
Falls
Let's just gather information.
I'll go talk to people who might know.
I'm counting on you.
Principal Canceled Password
I'm not getting any hits.
We'll have to crowdsource this.
Hello? Saori-san?
I want to ask you something.
Live streaming is an option, too.
To anime fans all across the world,
my name is Kamiigusa Alice.
I'm looking for a certain anime.
I call on the entirety of your anime knowledge.
Hello
Who's she?
High school girl?
It's an homage to Midia and Dog of Decadence.
It pays huge respects to Super Dimension
Bonsai Micross and GahXephon.
It's an anime that got canceled
after the first episode.
LOL
She's cute
Alice-chan!
Cutie!
Schoolgirl~
Talking about anime?
What's going on?
Looking for an anime?
She's cute
Alice-chan!
Cutie!
Schoolgirl~
Talking about anime?
What's going on?
Looking for an anime?
One episode lel
Canceled after one episode
Alice-chan!
Cutie!
Schoolgirl~
Talking about anime?
What's going on?
Looking for an anime?
One episode lel
Canceled after one episode
Shitty anime lmao
Cutie!
Schoolgirl~
Talking about anime?
What's going on?
Looking for an anime?
One episode lel
Canceled after one episode
Shitty anime lmao
Eeeeehhhh
Schoolgirl~
Talking about anime?
What's going on?
Looking for an anime?
One episode lel
Canceled after one episode
Shitty anime lmao
Eeeeehhhh
LOLOLOLOLOL
Talking about anime?
What's going on?
Looking for an anime?
Canceled after one episode
One episode lel
Shitty anime lmao
Eeeeehhhh
LOLOLOLOLOL
What a legend
What's going on?
Looking for an anime?
One episode lel
Canceled after one episode
Shitty anime lmao
Eeeeehhhh
LOLOLOLOLOL
What a legend
Crap anime lol
Looking for an anime?
Eeeeehhhh
One episode lel
Canceled after one episode
Shitty anime lmao
Eeeeehhhh
LOLOLOLOLOL
What a legend
Crap anime lol
ShiT ANiMe
We need your help.
Any information will do.
She's cute.
What's that?
Anime Underground @ Almond♡BBS
Screenshot from NETVIDEOLIVE
Kamiigusa Channel lol
Oh man, she's cute lol
Who's that?
Hot girl incoming
She's cute
Who's that?
Hot girl incoming
Kamiigusa Alice-chan? Princess!
Mystery anime wanted!
Canceled after episode 1
Shit anime? lol
lolol
Looking for crap anime ;_;
Dunno
The fuck?
No one knows it
She's cute
She's mad cute lol
Alice-chan lolol
You don't know, huh?
Sorry, thanks.
Anything online?
People are talking about Alice-chan.
Wait, her?
Well, we're sure to have
some leads if it goes viral.
Anime took everything from me.
I met my friends and found
my dream because of anime.
It's a nightmare!
It's despair!
It's a treasure!
A treasure?
That anime?
Well, I mean, I just can't
figure out how to explain it.
It's actually an amazing anime, I swear.
Canceled after the first episode?
Yes, does that ring a bell?
Dunno.
Thank you.
Canceled after the first episode?
What was it...
Was it EterSym?
==============Such a crap anime, and there's
========no leads here, either. Is this a prank??
Could it be
→
EterSym?
Nishiazabu, get back to work.
Oh, right.
Isn't it EterSym?
KathKor
What're they?
Dunno
Does anyone know?
She's cute
Alice-chan's an angel
Money lol
Cut after the first episode
KathKor, maybe?
>EterSym
Yeah, the official title
KathKor
EterSym
I think the abbreviation is different in the east and west
Eternal something something
Anyway, the girl's cute lolololol
What? Is that yummy?
Ultra Katharsis Koritsi!
Eternal Symphony!
That's it!
We got the title!
All right.
That's not it?
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
How long ago was that aired?
What's Ultra Katharsis Koritsi about?
Dunno
It's a flop
It's complete garbage
King of letdowns
It's a sleep agent
Worthless
Junk Micross
Ultra Katharsis Koritsi
Crap anime
Huh? A new crap anime?
Welcome, king crap anime!
Eternal Symphony
That's old
Alice-chan! Alice-chan!
Found it in Brazil
Relicensed?
Licensed overseas
Alice-chan! Alice-chan!
The subtitle is Eternal Symphony?
It seems there is another me in this world.
You two chuunis would get along well.
We're getting a ton of replies.
We're trending!
A giant mech, protecting the world.
But the lever is a piano,
the old man gets blown away by a ball,
and the blue pendant on the girl's
chest emits a magic light.
the two die, leaving just the fish to live on.
The angels arrive.
That was the end of the first episode.
I was so excited, waiting for the next story.
And yet the next week, and the
week after, it never aired.
That's because the director put a
lid on the second episode onward.
No way, we're going viral.
Senpai!
A fan sent me a link.
Isn't this...
Ultra Katharsis Koritsi.
Could this be...
You know the director behind
Ultra Katharsis Koritsi: Eternal Symphony?
He's...
right in front of you.
Whoa!
I'm a huge, huge, huge fan.
It's a treasure.
I love it!
Okay, okay.
So my work touched someone's heart.
And that became that piece of shit anime?!
Everything's fallen into place.
We're here!
Kaikai!
Mikocchi.
The password wasn't "catharsis."
"Katharsis" is a Greek word.
Philosopher Aristotle described it
as the purification of the mind.
Minoa!
Minoacchi!
Guys!
Thank goodness, Minoa.
Alice-chan.
You're drenched.
This is awful.
The floor's soaked.
Um...
Hold still.
What?
Oh, right.
Principal, take a look out the window.
What...
Alice 4lyf
Ultra Katharsis Koritsi!
Eternal Symphony!
Alice-chan!
Yes, just like them, I truly love anime.
Even now.
The effectiveness of a tragedy
is in the fierce emotions of fear
and sympathy that an audience experiences.
To be freed from such is
what is known as catharsis.
Bye-bye...
I love the club room.
This is where I feel most relaxed, too.
I quite agree, Neko-senpai.
Wait, that's too relaxing!
Miko-chan, you can understand
what Neko-senpai is saying?
Of course she can.
Now hold still.
This is weird.
What happened to everyone?
So that rain was real.
A yearbook.
It's the principal's.
No!
Wh-Why?
Aurora-senpai?
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
That sigh
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Ippo mae ni dete goran
Take a step forward, little lady
Chu!
nikkori tte shite goran
smile big and wide, little lady
Chu!
he no ji no kuchi fukureta kao mo tsuyoi kedo
that frown makes for a nice and tough face,
Chu!
Pokkari to ukanderu
but you're always walking hand-in-hand
Chu!
nakisou na fukidashi wo
with this sad little speech bubble
Chu!
kimi wa itsumo koneko no you ni tsurete iru
like a poor, lost kitten
Chu!
shumi ga koseiteki nandesu
My tastes are peculiar,
chotto
a little
marutto
so I
rikai dekiru yo
understand you completely
dakedo heart wa nozokanai
but I won't peek into your heart
kokoro no door
the door to your feelings
Daisuki na mono oikakete ikitai
I want to chase after what I love
ikou
so let's go
donna ni fukai kemono michi ya mori demo
No matter how many beasts infest the forest
nazo demo
or mysteries
ii nioi suru yokan sakimidareteru
It smells good, and I'm overflowing with anticipation
kyou wa good luck lilac
so good luck, lilac
good luck
lilac
ii koto ga aru
you have good things in your future
Ukiuki wiki hanakotoba wo shirabeta
Guess what? I Wikipedia'd the floriography
Maji ka?
Seriously?
"yuujou hatsukoi seishun no omoide"
and it stands for "friendship, first love, and teenaged memories"
Pride
and "pride"
Dare ni nitenakuttemo kamawanai
I don't care if I'm different from everyone else
moyamoya nara fukitobashichae
I'll just blow the depression away
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
that sigh
hint datta chucchu chu-lilas
was a hint
The next episode is the climax.
Let me tell you now—don't believe anything!
Otherwise...
You'll end up like this.