Previously on Anime-Gataris!
The student council has made a complaint
about the anime club's school festival event.
We all tried together to come
up with something to present.
Anime Proposal
"Schwein of Ockstadt"
Concept 1
An anime short script is a piece of cake.
And we decided to make an anime
short that Miko-chan proposed.
Anime Club Original Anime
Project Meeting!
13th Script Meeting
28th Script Meeting
You bitch!
We all worked hard together.
We were almost done, when...
Anime Club
Asagaya Minoa
Final
If you can't fill this up,
we'll deem your presentation a failure.
B. Seating Area
A. Special Stage
We might really end up
getting shut down this time.
My name is Yuirin!
I'm a magician that loves
excitement and explosions!
My name is...
My name...
Am I doing this right?
I'm not used to talking all cutesy.
Oh, what if I add some shouting?
My name is...
Yuirin!
That seems good.
Hi, can I say my line like that?
Nani wo shitete mo taikutsu na every day
No matter what I did, I found every day boring
Kokoro odoru you na tokimeki sagashiteta
I searched for something to make my heart dance
Shiranakatta yo kimi ni deau made
Until I met you, I never knew
Mahou mitai ni hirogaru brand new world
of this brand new world that unfolds like magic
Oshiete
So, tell me
Kimi to boku no aikotoba
our secret password
Tsunagaru tsunagaru
It'll connect us
Yuuki wo dashite
so let it be your courage
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can be even stronger
Tsuyoku nareru ki ga suru yo
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Boku ni wa nai kimi aru mono
As you complement and complete me
Awasareba saikyou ni!
I become the best I can be!
Hitori yori kimi to nara motto
I can shine even brighter
Kira kira ni kagayaku no
now that I'm with you and no longer alone
Kimi no "suki" boku no "suki" ga
Mixing your love with my love
Majiwareba saikou ni!
brings out the best in me!
Kimi to nara saikou ni!
With you, I'll be the best I can be!
Wait, Tsubaki.
I'll be looking forward to it,
Anime Club President.
P-President!
Pardon us.
Erica-senpai, any luck with the
student council president?
How are we supposed to fill that huge venue?
There are a ton of unfinished scenes in the anime.
The ending dance scene is nowhere near done, too.
I know.
What should we do?
Don't worry, Minoa-chan.
Nakano-senpai.
Even if it doesn't get finished,
we should present it.
It'll be a testament to our anime club's existence.
A testament to our existence, huh?
No, I don't want it to be unfinished.
I...
Minoa...
There's just no way to finish
it on time, given our schedule.
There's nothing more we can do.
Everyone's really tired.
I can't blame them.
If I, as the director, called it quits...
Sorry, everyone.
Give me a day to think things through.
Mii-chan?
What's wrong? You haven't even had dinner.
Onee-chan...
I had no idea.
Sorry, we can't use the
dubbing room anymore, either.
Too bad.
I was looking forward to it.
I mean, I'm Cute Girl A.
It's a great scene.
You show up looking really sharp,
and for the ending, we had the dance
scene that Mom choreographed for us.
That looks awesome.
It's not done yet, though.
Use this.
It's a DAT recorder.
You can record short lines at home.
Dad.
I was really happy to see you
working hard towards something.
Listen, Minoa!
Remember how it was on AKIBAKO?
Anime production is always
a race against time.
Every moment, up to the
minute it airs, is put to use.
Why do they do that?
Why else?
It's for the sake of the fans looking
forward to the completed anime.
For the people watching anime!
Don't you remember being excited about
the upcoming anime when you were little?
Now it's your turn to make anime.
Don't you ever give up,
no matter how tough it gets.
You have two days, including tomorrow.
Two days is enough to finish a new book!
A new book? What?
Oh, that's, well...
Why are you getting so intense over anime?
Dad, are you...
That's right, Dad's an otaku.
S-Since when?!
I had no idea.
Oh, didn't you meet him in summer by the sea?
By the sea?
Wait, he was at the event?
He's there every year.
It's his purpose in life.
It's over!
All this effort to put together the
perfect, dignified father image!
It's all over!
You've never been dignified, though.
That's not true.
You were really badass
preaching about anime, Dad.
Minoa...
You finally understand!
I'm so lucky to have such great daughters.
Anyway, I'm going to borrow this.
I don't know if it's worth recording.
We might not be able to finish the anime.
You're the director, aren't you?
Y-Yeah.
So just talk to everyone tomorrow
about what you want to do.
What I want to do?
That's right.
It's just like a sports club.
The coach's passion brings the team together
and points everyone towards one goal, right?
Onee-chan...
Okay, here goes Cute Girl A.
Man A is here, too.
You're too close!
You hit me.
Not even Mom's hit me.
Come on, now, don't lie.
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
Anime Club (6)
Guys...
Meet up at the club room during
lunch break tomorrow!
I'm turning.
Minoa, how's the anime coming along?
I-It's almost done.
Sorry I can't help out in class too much.
Leave that to me.
Break a leg.
Thanks.
What's up? It's marked as read,
but they're ignoring you?
Why are you up there?
I don't need to explain myself to you!
Jeez, it's not that they're
reading it and ignoring me.
So they're legit ignoring you.
You didn't have to be that blunt about it.
No one's read it since yesterday.
Maybe it's no use.
They probably half-assed it because they
didn't think they could finish it to begin with.
That's not true!
We spent the last three
months making that anime.
We hit so many problems.
But we got this far because everyone helped out.
I could never have done anything by myself.
I'm the director. I know better than
anyone how hard everyone's been working.
So I can't give up now.
I... I...
Good.
Scene
I'm not giving up.
I'm going to do everything I can.
Scene
Sorry I'm late.
I've brought the unfinished
scenes from the art club.
I finished the novel adaptation.
I thought we could use scenes from
our production for the ending.
I edited it together.
I recorded the missing sound effects at home.
I studied the latest shows and
finished up the action scenes.
Good nap.
G-Guys...
Why?
I thought you didn't read my LINE message.
Your LINE message?
Oh...
I was focused on work the whole night.
I never saw it.
My phone was turned off.
Thank goodness, I totally thought...
You thought what?
...that you'd all given—
But our director hadn't
given up at all, Minoacchi.
You're right.
All right!
That aside, it's going to be tough
getting people to fill the seats.
Give up now, and it's over.
A famous quote from Slash Dunk.
We need to learn from school club anime, huh?
School club anime...
What is it?
Guys, I think we can use these.
Club Anime Talk!
Participants wanted!
What's Club Anime Talk?
You get to stand on a special
stage to talk about your club,
as we watch club anime together.
For the baseball club it would be Ace of Bench,
and for tennis it would be Fresh Prince of Tennis.
Wow, that takes me back.
I used to watch that when I was little.
We should be able to present our club's work
and all enjoy the school festival together.
We want to make it into a festival
where people with all kinds of tastes
can discuss it to their hearts' content.
That sounds fun.
I'm in!
Me, too!
And me!
Me, too.
It's futile.
My turn already?!
It's not the ending yet.
Next episode, the legendary idol... Wait, no.
Killer artwork...
Wait, no time?
Hang on!
Alice
Can't
Make
Enough
Money
There! There it is!
Retake!
Man, don't point the camera
at me without warning.
I'm not good at ad lib.
All right, I'm off!
Mii-chan, you have a milk mustache.
Good luck, Mii-chan.
I'll go watch with my friend.
Okay.
Thanks.
Minoa.
Believe in me who believes in you!
That's from Guden Daran, isn't it?
Thanks, Dad.
I'll see you later.
See you.
Now, time to get ready to go.
Dad, what's with the outfit?
Look at Minoa working so hard.
As her dad, I have to do what I can, too!
You're great, dear.
Honey...
Rein it in a little...
Oh right, you invited your friends, didn't you?
Yeah.
Mii-chan's going to be surprised.
This way.
Form two lines. Don't shove.
Anime Club screening event.
Make sure you come along!
I hope you can all make it.
Anything for you, Senpai!
Anime Screening
Anime Club
''Original''
Anime Screening
Anime Club
''Original''
Anime Screening
Anime Club
''Original''
Anime Screening
Anime Club
''Original''
Anime Screening
Anime Club
''Original''
Anime Screening
Here.
Anime Club
''Original''
Anime Screening
This is the one.
I'll be there.
Thank you.
That girl reminds me of someone.
This is the Club Anime Talk and anime
screening hosted by the Anime Club.
Nihao, Minoa.
Beibei-chan!
Why are you here?
Mii-chan.
Onee-chan!
She's my classmate.
I told her about you,
and she said she knew you.
You're studying at my sister's school?
Making anime in a club?
Japan's so amazing!
I'd like to make anime when I get back to China.
It's fun.
Feel free to ask me anything.
I will!
President, the Anime Club...!
They currently have roughly 80% of the space filled.
Are we really going with that title?
There isn't so much as a
trace of the original script.
Can't I have at least that much?
I got the audience warmed up.
Are you ready?
I did my best to finish the missing scenes right up until the last minute, but...
But we couldn't finish the ending song and art.
Thank you.
We did the best we could.
Thank you all very much.
I have an idea.
B-But that's...
I'm sure you can pull it off, Minoa-chan.
I think it's worth giving it a shot unrehearsed.
I feel uneasy about this,
but I'll take one for the team.
I can't think of anything to be uneasy about.
I have nothing but hope!
All right.
I'll give it a try.
The wait is over.
We'll hereby begin the screening of
the anime club's original anime short.
"Space Girl Magical Robot Travels to Another World,
Where She Sings and Dances,
but in the End She Ascends to Heaven
and the Two Are United"
"Space Girl Magical Robot Travels to Another World,
Where She Sings and Dances,
but in the End She Ascends to Heaven
and the Two Are United"
"Space Girl Magical Robot Travels to Another World,
Where She Sings and Dances,
but in the End She Ascends to Heaven
and the Two Are United"
Here we go.
AliceRobo, away!
Monies!
Stand!
Get up, AliceRobo!
Not enough money.
Shutting down.
Transform!
Hear me!
Warrior of love, hope, and magic!
Magical Girl Magical Erica!
Let's end this, AliceRobo!
Come, Kaikai Blade!
Behold, Mad King Kai has
descended from the nether world
to cast the most powerful defense spell!
Satanic Extra Strongest Shield!
What are you, delusional?
Don't die, Grandpa!
Grandpa!
Dad will not die!
He will be reborn!
Bath's ready, dear.
Maya!
Hurry up and die.
So long as AliceRobo is disabled,
you don't stand a chance.
Hang in there.
I have your back.
My name is Yuirin!
I'm a magician that loves
excitement and explosions!
Now, everyone!
We all need to cheer for AliceRobo.
Go, AliceRobo!
AliceRobo!
Get up, you lump of scrap!
Payment complete.
AliceRobo, fire the Money Beam!
Money!
I-Is this the power of money?!
Good luck.
Ringon... Ringon...
W-Wait, why me?
Let go!
Are you telling me to fly?
Don't worry.
We can fly.
A-And the two are united in heaven.
Meow.
And peace on Earth is protected again.
Monies!
That was pretty good, huh?
Yeah.
That was great!
Hey, what about the ending?
I want to see more!
All right, everyone, it's time for the ending.
Start the music.
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
That sigh
Yume no sei da chucchu chu-lilas
was because of my dream
Ippo mae ni dete goran
Take a step forward, little lady
Chu!
nikkori tte shite goran
smile big and wide, little lady
Chu!
he no ji no kuchi fukureta kao mo tsuyoi kedo
that frown makes for a nice and tough face,
Chu!
Pokkari to ukanderu
but you're always walking hand-in-hand
Chu!
nakisou na fukidashi wo
with this sad little speech bubble
Chu!
kimi wa itsumo koneko no you ni tsurete iru
like a poor, lost kitten
Chu!
shumi ga koseiteki nandesu
My tastes are peculiar,
chotto
a little
marutto
so I
rikai dekiru yo
understand you completely
dakedo heart wa nozokanai
but I won't peek into your heart
kokoro no door
the door to your feelings
Daisuki na mono oikakete ikitai
I want to chase after what I love
ikou
so let's go
donna ni fukai kemono michi ya mori demo
No matter how many beasts infest the forest
nazo demo
or mysteries
ii nioi suru yokan sakimidareteru
It smells good, and I'm overflowing with anticipation
kyou wa good luck lilac
so good luck, lilac
good luck
lilac
ii koto ga aru
you have good things in your future
Ukiuki wiki hanakotoba wo shirabeta
Guess what? I Wikipedia'd the floriography
Maji ka?
Seriously?
"yuujou hatsukoi seishun no omoide"
and it stands for "friendship, first love, and teenaged memories"
Pride
and "pride"
Dare ni nitenakuttemo kamawanai
I don't care if I'm different from everyone else
moyamoya nara fukitobashichae
I'll just blow the depression away
Tameiki wa chucchu chu-lilas
that sigh
hint datta chucchu chu-lilas
was a hint
Good job, kids!
That choreography...
That choreography is the legendary...
Minoa!
Alice-chan!
Miko-chan!
Stop, Minoa, I can't breathe.
I guess this is all right once in a while.
Minoacchi!
I can't help but be moved to tears!
That was an amazing concert,
my little kittens.
Yes.
My most sincere apologies, Principal.
That was great, President!
Thanks.
Let's keep going.
What did we have next?
Hello?
It's your favorite, President.
Stay longer? Of course.
Oh, I'll have a cola.
One more for cola.
Oh, I'll have French fries.
French fries and honey toast, please.
Pretty Fairy!
Enemies of Mother Earth,
cease your evil deeds!
Cease them at once!