Episode 13: "Hacka Dolls Can Handle Anything, Even Comiket"
Huh? You're getting married?
Yep!
C-Congratulations.
Thanks.
I hope you find someone soon too, Aya-chan!
Yeah...
Oh, that's right.
I decided to go for it and make
a doujinshi for this year's Comiket.
Are you going as a guest or...
Aya-chan, you're still into that?
I quit being an otaku ages ago.
Oh... I see...
Oh, but you could still attend as a fan...
Aya-chan...
Just move on already.
Yuri-chan...
You're not young anymore.
You need to start thinking about your future and your career.
Well...
You need to face reality.
No peeking, you pervert!
What's happening?
All oden items were 70 yen!
We are, as always...
Your Personal Entertainment AIs, Hacka Dolls!
What is it this time?
Ahem!
Due to our stupendous efforts,
you reclaimed your otaku status
and began producing your doujinshi for Comiket.
Which is almost here!
So we came to see how your manuscript is coming—
Huh?
Please leave.
What's happened?!
After all we did to advance you!
What in the world happened?
Hey, where's the rest of this?
Just stop it, please!
My manuscript is in there!
What?
Why?
Why? Because I realized something.
It's time to stop being an otaku and face reality.
Don't say that! Let's go to Comi—
I'm not going!
Ayame-san...
Please leave.
Hacka Dolls? More like "hacks"!
All you do is force me to do what you want.
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
Don't ever come here again!
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
A man's life of 50 years under the sky
is nothing compared to
the age of this world.
Life is but a fleeting dream, an illusion—
Is there anything that lasts forever?
Are you sure you want to uninstall?
Hacka Doll
Uninstalled
Thank you for using our app.
Yes
No
#3-chan...
Yeah.
And you!
You look so happy.
Ayame-san, you look so happy!
You were having so much fun.
How can you suddenly hate it now?
Stop lying to yourself!
I don't hate it...
I just think I'm too old for it.
I can't keep running from reality...
You can't run from your feelings
and call it "running from reality"!
It's okay to like what you like!
Age has nothing to do with it!
I will advance you, Ayame-san!
I'll chase you to the ends of Hell
to advance you if I have to!
That is our duty as your Personal
Entertainment AIs, as Hacka Dolls!
I think!
You're crazy...
I'll make you crazy!
What?!
Er... I mean, I'll advance you like crazy!
Oh, fine!
All right already.
But I have to start from scratch,
since I crumpled it up.
There's no time left either.
Can you help me with my manuscript?
Of course!
Okay, time for some serious advancing!
I've gotta recharge first...
Hey! Don't fall asleep just yet!
I don't like this pairing...
Please don't say that.
Are we really going to get this done?
I am Chief Comiket!
My name is Comi-shima Ket-nosuke!
Please clear the way!
We're attending Comiket—
Little ones, you are nowhere near ready for Comiket.
Behold the other attendees!
Gimme five copies of the new book!
What a lovely day!
Can I look at this?
Sure.
Y-You mustn't run at Comiket!
#3-chan, watch out!
#3-chan!
Why did this happen?
Okay, that's enough.
Z-Zero-nee?
If you can't even advance someone at this level,
then it's time you were scrapped!
Not at Comiket!
#1-chan!
#2? #3?
You're next, #1.
How dare you turn my best friends into dust?!
Well, shall we begin?
Z-Zero-nee?!
#4-chan?!
#1... If we don't do something, #0 will destroy
this convention center and everyone in it.
#4...
Please protect my beloved
convention center and otaku...
Stay out of this, you miserable failure.
Y-You transformed?!
Impossible! I can't be...
#2... #3... #4... You guys...
#1-chan!
#1!
#1...
I'm not sure how, but you did it!
You guys...
Yeah.
I did it! I advanced!
#1-chan. #1-chan!
I advanced...
You were fast asleep, #1-chan.
Well, we did pull an all-nighter.
Huh? It was a dream?
No way!
Um, did we do a good job advancing your work?
It really was crazy.
But...
It was fun, and we did finish the fan comic.
So I guess you did advance my work.
Let me tell you what love is
Thank you so much!
Let's bring all these dreams together
I'd like that in writing.
Don't be shy or run away!
Ditto.
Well, since you've advanced me plenty,
you should go advance lots of other people.
You can put your faith in me!
Even if your mind is flustered and confused
I'm sure they're waiting for you.
Good morning.
Your body will stay true and move the way it should!
Day 1 of Comic Market 89 will now commence.
Even for just a second, you'll realize that there's many paths before you
Well, let's get going!
We need to keep advancing people.
Yes! We Personal Entertainment AIs,
Hacka Dolls, can handle anything!
Which one do I pick? Won't you help me choose?
Even Comiket!
Let's keep touching today, baby!
How do you want to feel?
I can be in the minority or the majority
They're both just as fun to me!
Let's keep touching today, baby!
So won't you softly touch me, baby?
I just can't wait to be with you!
I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!